horizon but it would be a seminar most of you finished and unfinished but
수평선 그러나 그것은 당신의 대부분이 완료 세미나 및 미완성 것입니다하지만
against ok get some decent ok I'll be holding off makeup office hours right
확인 좀 괜찮은 확인을 얻을에 나는 메이크업 근무 시간 권리를 보유 할 수 있습니다
after this class assignment 2 will be released tomorrow or day after tomorrow
이 클래스 할당 한 후이 내일 이후 내일 또는 일 발매 예정
we haven't fully finalize the date or still working on it and we're changing
우리는 완벽하게 일을 마무리하거나 여전히 작업을 우리는 변화하고하지 않은
it from last year and so we are in process of developing and we hope to
그것은 작년 그래서 우리는 개발의 과정에서 우리는 희망
have it as soon as possible
가능한 한 빨리이
its meeting but an occasional so you do want to get started on that ASAP once
그 모임하지만 가끔 당신은 최대한 빨리 한 번 그에서 시작하려는 않도록
it's released we might be adjusting the due date or somethin to because it is
우리가이 때문에 기한 또는 뭔가를 조정 될 수 있습니다 발표이야
slightly larger and yes so so will be shuffling some of these things around
약간 큰 그래 그래서 그래서 주위에 이런 것들의 일부를 셔플한다
and also the grading scheme of the stuff is just tentative and subject to change
또한 재료의 등급을 매기는 방식은 임시 변경 될 수 있습니다
because we're still trying to figure out the course it's still relatively new and
우리는 여전히 비교적 새로운 아직 코스를 알아 내기 위해 노력하고 있기 때문에
a lot of it is changing so those are just some heads up before we start in
그것의 많은 우리가 시작하기 전에 사람들은 그냥 머리까지입니다 그래서 변화
terms of your project proposal by the way which is due in roughly 10 days I
약 10 일 예정이다 그런데 프로젝트 제안서의 조건 I
wanted to just bring up a few points because you'll be thinking about your
당신에 대해 생각하고있을 것이기 때문에 몇 가지 포인트를 불어 넣고 싶었 당신의
projects and some of you might have some misconceptions about what makes a good
무슨 좋은하게 대해 프로젝트와 여러분 중 일부는 약간의 오해가있을 수 있습니다
or bad project so just two of them the most common one probably is that people
나쁜 프로젝트는 그래서 그냥이 그들을 가장 일반적인 하나는 아마 그 사람입니다
are hesitant to work with data sets that are small because they think that that's
그들이 그이 있다고 생각하기 때문에 작은 데이터 세트로 작업 할 주저
require a huge amount of data training and this is true there's hundreds of
데이터 교육의 엄청난 금액을 요구하고이 수백 거기에 해당하는
millions of prime minister to come out and they need training but actually for
총리의 수백만 나올하고 그들은 훈련이 필요하지만, 사실에 대한
your purposes in the project this is kind of a mess this is not something you
프로젝트에 목적이 뭔가 당신이 엉망의 종류, 그렇지 않습니다
have to worry about a lot you can work with smaller data sets its ok the reason
당신이 작은 데이터로 작업 할 수 있습니다 많은 걱정하는 이유의 확인을 설정
it's ok is that we have this process that will go into much more detail later
우리가이 과정을 가지고 나중에 더 많은 세부 사항으로 이동합니다되는 괜찮아요
in a class called fine-tuning and the thing is that in practice you rarely
미세 조정과 일이라는 클래스가 실제로 당신이 거의 없다
ever trained these giant camel response crash almost always do this retraining
지금이 거대한 낙타 응답 충돌 훈련을 거의 항상이 재교육을
and planting process so the way this will work
및 심기 처리 방식 때문에이 작동합니다
look like it's almost always take a commercial network he trained on some
거의 항상 그 일부에 대한 교육을 상용 네트워크를 취할 것처럼
large data set up say images likes a huge amount of data and then you're
설정 대용량 데이터 이미지는 당신이있어 대량의 데이터를 좋아하는 말
interested in some other data set right there and you can train your comment on
바로 거기 설정 다른 데이터에 관심이 당신은 당신의 코멘트를 훈련 할 수있다
your small business that will turn it here and then we'll transfer it over
중소 기업 여기를 설정하고 우리는 그것을 통해 전송할 수 있습니다 그
there and the way this transfer works like it is
거기 그것이 같은 방식이 이전 작품
so here's a schematic of a comedy show network we start for the image and talk
그래서 여기에 우리가 이미지와 이야기에 대한 시작 코미디 쇼 네트워크의 개략도이다
and we'll go through a series of layers down to a classifier so you're used to
당신이 사용하고, 그래서 우리는 아래 분류에 층의 시리즈를 통해 갈거야
this but we haven't of course talked about the specific players here but we
이것은 그러나 우리는 물론 여기에 특정 선수에 대해 이야기하지만하지 않은 우리
take that image net free trade network we trained on a minute and then we
우리를 우리가 분에 대한 교육을 해당 이미지 순 자유 무역 네트워크를 가지고 다음
chopped off the top layer the classifier with chopped off take it away and we
그것은 멀리 가기 층 오프 다진 테이크로 분류를 다진 우리
train the entire commercial network has a fixed feature extractor and so you can
전체 상용 네트워크는 고정 된 특징 추출기를 가지고 훈련 등을 수행 할 수 있습니다
put that feature extractor on top of your new dataset and you're just going
새 데이터 세트의 상단에 그 특징 추출기를 넣어 당신은 단지거야
to swap in a different layer that performs a classification on top and so
그래서 상단에 분류를 수행하는 다른 층에 교환합니다
depending on how much data you have your own going to train the last layer of
당신이 당신의 자신의 마지막 층을 훈련하기 위하여려고 얼마나 많은 데이터에 따라
your network or you can do fine tuning where you actually back propagate
당신이 실제로 다시 전파 경우 네트워크하거나 미세 조정을 할 수 있습니다
through some portions of the combat and get more data you're going to do back
그리고 전투의 일부를하면 다시 할 거 야 더 많은 데이터를 얻을
propagation deeper through the network and in particular the spring training
깊은 네트워크를 통해 특히 봄 훈련에 전파
sample image net people do this for you so there's a huge line of people who've
한 사용자의 거대한 라인이 그래서 샘플 이미지 그물 사람들은 당신을 위해 이렇게
trained comes home networks will reluctance of time weeks on different
다른에 시간 주 홈 네트워크가됩니다 온다 훈련을 꺼리는
datasets and then they upload the weight of the comment on line is there
데이터 세트와 라인이에 그들은 주석의 무게를 업로드
something called a couple models who for example and these are all these
뭔가 예를 들어 이들은 모든입니다 몇 가지 모델을 호출
commercial networks have been preaching on large data sets they already have
상업 네트워크는 이미 대규모 데이터 세트에 설교 한
lots of the parameters learned and see just take the surrounding swapping your
매개 변수가 많이 배웠 단지 주변 교환을 참조하여
datacenter you find him through the network so basically if you don't have a
당신이없는 경우 데이터 센터는 그렇게 기본적으로 네트워크를 통해 그를 찾을
lot of data that's okay and you just take a preacher in combat and just fine
데이터를 많이 괜찮아 당신은 전투와 잘에서 설교자을 그
tune it and so don't be afraid to work with small dataset it's going to work
조정을하고 그래서 일 것 작은 데이터 세트로 작업하는 것을 두려워하지 않는다
out of the second thing that we saw some problems with last time is that people
우리가 지난 시간에 몇 가지 문제가 보았던 두 번째 것은 밖으로 사람들이다
think they have infinite computer and this is also a metal just like to point
그들은 무한한 컴퓨터가이 단지를 가리 키도록 좋아도 금속 생각
out don't be overly ambitious and what you propose these things take a while to
아웃 지나치게 야심 찬하고 당신이 제안하는 어떤 것들은 잠시에 적용되지 않습니다
train you don't have too many GPUs you're going to have to hyper
당신이 하이퍼해야 할거야 너무 많은 GPU를이없는 훈련
optimization there's a few things you have to worry about here so we had some
최적화는 우리가 몇 가지 있었다 있도록 여기에 대해 걱정할 필요가 몇 가지있다
projects last year where people proposed projects of training on very large data
사람들이 매우 큰 데이터에 대한 교육의 프로젝트를 제안 프로젝트 지난해
sets and you just don't have the time so be mindful of that and yeah you'll get a
설정하고 당신은 시간이되도록 염두이 없어 그래, 당신은 얻을 것이다
better sense as we go through the class and what is or is not possible given
더 나은 감각 우리는 클래스를 통해 갈 것입니다 또는 제공 할 수 없습니다로
your computer constraints ok we're going to dive into lectures are there any
우리가 강의에 뛰어거야 확인 컴퓨터 제약이 어떤 있습니다
administrative things that I may be left out that you like to ask about it
나는 당신이 그것에 대해 물어보고 싶은 것을 남아있을 수 있습니다 관리 일
ok good so we're going to dive into the material we have quite a bit of it today
확인 좋은 그래서 우리는 오늘날 우리가 꽤있는 재료로 다이빙을거야
so just as a reminder woodworking industry mark the passing grade in the
그래서 그냥 알림 목공 산업으로의 합격 점수를 표시
center for training
교육 센터
networks and basically the four-step process training a neural network is as
네트워크 기본적 신경 네트워크를 훈련하는 4 단계 공정은 그대로
simple as 123 for you sample your data so a batch of your data from a dataset
당신이 데이터 세트에서 데이터의 배치 귀하의 데이터를 샘플링 123 간단
you forward it through your network to compute the Los
당신은 로스를 계산하기 위해 네트워크를 통해 전달
propagate to complete your radiance and the new primary update or you tweak your
당신의 생기 새 차 업데이트를 완료 전파하거​​나 조정할 당신의
weight slightly in the direction of the ingredients and so when you end up
약간 재료 등의 방향으로 무게가 끝날 때
repeating this process that really what this comes down to is an optimization
정말 어떤이가 내려 오는 것은 최적화가이 과정을 반복
problem wherein to wait space were converging into areas of the white space
공간을 대기하는 것을 특징으로 문제는 공백의 영역으로 수렴 하였다
we have low loss and that means are correctly classifying or training center
우리는 낮은 손실과 그 수단 제대로 분류하거나 교육 센터를
and we saw that these very large and i flash disk image of altering sheen
우리는이 매우 큰 것을보고 나는 변경 광택의 디스크 이미지를 플래시
basically these are huge computational graphs and we need to do back
기본적으로이 거대한 계산 그래프는 그리고 우리는 할 필요가
propagation through them and so we talked about intuition some back
그들을 통해 전파 그래서 우리는 직관 몇 가지 다시 이야기하고
propagation and the fact that it's really just a recursive application of
전파와 정말 그냥 재귀 응용 프로그램의 사실
general from back on the circuit to the front where we're changing gradients
우리가 그라디언트를 변경하고 전면에 회로 다시에서 일반
through all the local operations we looked at some implementations of this
모든 로컬 작업을 통해 우리는이 일부 구현 보았다
can quickly with the forward backward API on both coasts competition graph and
수 신속하게 모두 해안 경쟁 그래프에서 앞으로 뒤로 API와
also in terms of its nodes which also implement the same API and do for
또한 노드의 관점에서 이는 동일한 API를 구현을 위해 할
propagation and backward propagation we looked at specific examples in Portugal
전파 및 역 전파 우리는 포르투갈 구체적인 예 보았다
cafe and I drew this analogy that these are kind of like your illegal blocks
카페와 나는이 당신 불법 블록 같은 종류의 것을이 비유를 그린
these layers are gates are your little blocks from which you build out to the
이 층은 게이트 당신이에 구축하는 당신의 작은 블록입니다입니다
intercom system that works then we talked about neural networks first
다음 작품 인터콤 시스템은 먼저 신경 네트워크에 대해 이야기
without the bring stuff and basically what that amounts to is we're making
물건을 가지고 그것은 우리가 만드는 것입니다 금액 기본적으로 무엇을하지 않고
this which goes from your image to class course more complex and then we looked
클래스 코스로 이미지에서 진행되는이 더 복잡하고 우리는 보았다
at bill that works from the brain stuff perspective where this is a chronology
법안에이 연대기는 뇌 물건의 관점에서 작품을
of neuron and what we're doing is we're stopping these emails and letters oK so
신경과 우리가하고있는 것입니다으로 우리는 확인 그래서 이러한 이메일과 편지를 중지하고
that's roughly what we're doing right now and we're going to talk in this
그것은 우리가 지금 무슨 일을하는지 대략 그리고 우리는이 얘기하는거야
class about this process of training early works effectively ok so we're
훈련이 프로세스에 대한 클래스는 초기 우린 있도록 효과적으로 확인 작업
going to go into that before I dive into the details of it I just wanted to kind
내가 다이빙을하기 전에 세부 사항에 해당로 갈 난 그냥 싶었 종류
of pull out and give you a zoomed out the you up a bit of a history of how
밖으로 당겨주고 당신은 최대에게 어떻게 역사를 조금 축소
this evolved over time if you try to find where the spilled oil comes from
당신이 유출 된 기름이 어디​​에서 오는지 발견하려고하면이 시간이 지남에 진화
where the first proposed and so on
여기서 제 등등 제안
you probably will go back to roughly 1964 Frank rosenblatt in 1957 was
당신은 아마 1957 년에 약 1,964 프랭크 로젠 블랏으로 돌아 갈 것이었다
playing around with something called perceptrons and the perceptron basically
뭔가라는 퍼셉트론 즈 (Perceptrons)와 기본적으로 퍼셉트론과 장난
it ended up being this implementation and hardware so you have to like
당신이 좋아하는 그래서이 구현 및 하드웨어 었죠
they do just write code right now actually had to build these things out
그들은 단지 실제로이 일을 구축했다 지금 코드를 작성 않습니다
from circuits and electronics in these times for most part and submitted the
이 시간에 회로와 전자 기기에서 대부분의 경우와 제출
perceptron roughly was this function here and it looks very similar to what
퍼셉트론은 대략이 기능 여기이었고, 그것은 매우 유사 모습
we are familiar with its Justin only explicitly but then the activation
우리는 그 다음 활성화 만 명시 적으로 저스틴을 잘 알고 있지만,
function which were used to as a signal that activation function was actually a
활성화 함수 실제로되었다는 신호로 사용 된 함수
step function it was either 10 it was a binary step function and so since this
스텝 함수는 그것이이 때문에 바이너리 스텝 함수 등이었다 중 10이었다
is my new step function you'll notice that this is not differentiable
나의 새로운 단계 기능은 당신이이 미분 아니라는 것을 알 수 있습니다
operation so they were not able to back propagate through this in fact the cost
작업은 그래서 그들은 비용 사실이 통해 전파 백업 할 수 없었다
of the backpropagation for training neural networks have to come much later
교육 신경 네트워크를위한 역 전파의 훨씬 나중에 올 필요
and so they came up with these binary stepwise functions perceptron and they
그래서 그들은 이러한 이진 단계적으로 기능 퍼셉트론 그들은 함께했다
came up with these learning rules and so this is kind of an ad hoc specified
이러한 학습 규칙에 와서 그래서 이것은 임시 지정의 종류
learning rule that tweaked the weights to make the desired outcome from the
가중치를 쥐게 규칙을 학습하는 것은에서 원하는 결과를 만들려면
perceptron match the true of the true desire to balance but there was no
퍼셉트론 일치하는 진정한 욕망의 진정한는 균형을하지만, 거기에 아무
concept of a loss function there was no concept of backpropagation his DS DS ad
손실 함수의 개념은 역 전파 그의 DS DS 광고의 개념이 없었다
hoc rules which when you look at them they kind of almost do background but
당신이 그들을 볼 때 그들이 종류의 거의 배경을 특별 규칙 만
it's kind of funny because of the step function which is not differentiable and
이 때문에 미분하지 않고 스텝 기능의 종류의 재미
then people started to stop these so in 1960 with the advent of Madeline
다음 사람들은 매들린의 출현으로 1960 년에 있으므로이를 중지 시작
Madeline by woodrow enough they started to take these perceptron like things and
우드로 매들린이 충분히들은 것 같은이 퍼셉트론을 시작했고,
stuff them into the first multi-layer perceptron networks and this was still
제 다층 퍼셉트론 망로 물건 이는 여전히
all done in this Electronics and LG and actually building out from Porter and
모든 전자와 LG에서 수행 실제로 포터로부터 구축
but still there's no back propagation at this time this was all of these rules
하지만 여전히이이 모든 규칙을했다이 경우에는 다시 전파가 없습니다
that they come up with in terms of like thinking about trying to flip it and
그들이 측면에서 가지고 올 것을의 그것을 뒤집기 시도에 대해 생각하기 추천하고
seeing if it works better or not and it was kind of there was no view of
더 나은 여부를 작동하고 가지의 더보기가 없었다 경우보고
backpropagation at this time and so roughly nineteen sixty people got very
이 시점에서 역 전파 등 약 1960년 사람들은 매우있어
excited and building up the circuits and they thought that you know this could go
흥분과 회로를 구축하고 그들은 당신이 갈 수 알고 있다고 생각
really far we can have these circuits that learn you have to remember that
정말 지금까지 우리는 내용이 회로는 것을 기억해야 할 수 있습니다
back then the concept of programming was very explicit you write a series of
그때 프로그래밍의 개념은 매우 명시했다 당신은 일련의 쓰기
instructions for a computer and this is the first time that people are thinking
컴퓨터에 대한 지침이 사람들이 생각하는이 처음이다
about this kind of data driven approach where you have some kind of a circuit
이러한 종류의 데이터는 접근 방식을 기반에 대해 당신은 회로의 일종 곳
that can learn and so this was at the time a huge conceptual leap that people
이 배울 수 있고, 그래서 이것은 시간 사람들이 큰 개념적 도약에 있었다
are very excited about these networks with not actually end up working
실제로 작업 끝나지 이러한 네트워크에 대한 매우 흥분
very well right away in terms of 1964 example they got slightly over excited
잘 바로 1964 예 측면에서 그들은 흥분을 통해 약간있어
and over promised and the slightly under delivered and so throughout the period
이상은 약속​​과 약간 아래에 따라서 기간 동안 전달
of nineteen seventies actually in the field was very quiet and not much
열 아홉 칠십의 실제 현장에서 매우 조용하고 많은 아니었다
research has been done next boost actually came about roughly 1986 and in
연구는 다음 부스트 사실에 대한 대략 1986 년에 와서 완료되었습니다
1986 people there was this influential paper that basically he is the first
1천9백86명이 기본적으로 자신이 처음입니다이 영향력있는 논문이었다
time that you see back propagation like rules in a nicely presented format and
당신이 잘되게 형식으로 규칙 등의 전파를 다시 볼 시간과
so this is really hard in 10 and Wilson and they were playing with multi-layer
그래서 이것은 (10)와 윌슨에 정말 열심히 그리고 그들은 여러 층으로 연주했다
perceptrons and this is the first time when you go to the paper we actually see
퍼셉트론 즈 (Perceptrons) 그리고 당신이 우리가 실제로 볼 수있는 종이에 갈 때이 처음이다
something that looks like a back propagation and so at this point they
이 시점에서 다시 전파 등처럼 보이는 뭔가 그들이
already discarded this idea of ad-hoc rules and become really the lock
이미 임시 규칙이 아이디어를 폐기 정말 자물쇠가
function and talked about back propagation gradient descent and so on
기능 등 전파 그라데이션 하강에 대해 다시 이야기하고
and so this time people get excited again in 1986 because they felt that
그들이 있다고 생각하기 때문에 그래서이 시간 사람들은 1986 년에 다시 흥분
they now had a principal nice credit assignment kind of skiing by
그들은 지금 스키의 주요 좋은 신용 할당 종류를했다
backpropagation and they could train networks the problem unfortunately was
역 전파 그들이 네트워크를 훈련 할 수있는 문제가 있었다 불행히도
that when they tried to scale up these networks to make them deeper or larger
그들은 이러한 네트워크를 확장하려고 할 때 그들을 깊이 이상 만드는 것을
they didn't work very well compared to some of the other things that might be
그들이 할 수있는 다른 것들 중 일부에 비해 매우 잘 작동하지 않았다
your machine learning tool kits and so they just did not give a very good
당신의 기계 학습 도구 키트 그래서 그들은 그냥 아주 좋은을 포기하지 않았다
results at this time and training with get stuck and the competition was
이 시간과 훈련의 결과는 박히과 경쟁했다
basically not working very well especially he wanted to have largely
기본적으로 아주 잘 작동하지 특히​​ 그는 크게하고 싶어
networks and this was the case for actually roughly twenty years where
네트워크는이 사실 거의 이십년 곳의 경우와
again there was less research on your own works because somehow it wasn't
어떻게 든이 없었기 때문에 다시 자신의 작품에 적은 연구가 있었다
working very well and you can train because and in 2006 the research was a
연구는이 때문에 2006 년 아주 잘 작동하고 당신은 훈련 할 수있다
recent once again reinvigorated whether paper in science by Hinton and and
최근 다시 한번 소생 힌튼과과에 의해 과학 논문 여부
Russell had enough enough yet say his name but basically what they found here
러셀은 충분히 충분했다 아직 그의 이름을 말할하지만 그들은 여기 기본적으로 무엇을
was this was roughly the first time we can actually have likes a penalty or
이것은 우리가 실제로 할 수 있습니다 처음으로 페널티 킥을 추천 또는 약이었다
neural network that trains properly and what they did was instead of training
제대로 훈련하고 그들이 한 신경망 훈련 대신했다
all the layers like 10 layers by backpropagation a single pass they came
역 전파가 온 단일 패스 10 층 같은 모든 층
up with this unsupervised pre-training scheme using what's called restricted
제한이라는 무엇을 사용하여이 자율 사전 교육 방식에 최대
Boltzmann machine and so what this amounts to is you train your first layer
볼츠만 기계와이 첫 번째 층을 양성되는 금액 그래서 뭐
using an unsupervised objective and then you train your second layer on top of it
자율 목표를 사용하여 당신은 그 위에 두 번째 층을 훈련
and then third and fourth and then once all of these are trained then you put
다음 세 번째와 네 번째 다음 번에이 모든 당신이 넣어 다음 훈련
them all together and then you start back propagation then you start to
모두 함께 다음은 당신이 시작 전파를 다시 시작
fine-tuning step it was a two step process of first read the speech
먼저 음성 읽어 미세 조정 단계는 두 단계 프로세스이었다
stepwise through the layers and then we put them in and then back propagation
레이어를 통해 단계적으로, 그리고, 우리는에 넣어 다음 다시 전파
works and so this was the first time a back-propagation
작동하고 그래서 이것은 역 전파 처음이다
needed basically this initialization from the unsurprisingly training
놀라지 훈련에서 기본적으로이 초기화를 필요
otherwise they would not work out of luck from scratch and we're going to see
그렇지 않으면 그들은 처음부터 운이 작동하지 않을 것입니다 그리고 우리는 보게 될 것입니다
why in this lecture it's kind of tricky to get these indeed networks to train
왜이 강의에서이 훈련이 참으로 네트워크를 얻기 위해 가지 까다로운
from scratch using just backdrop and you have to really think about it and so it
처음부터 그냥 배경을 사용하여 그리고 당신이 정말로 그것에 대해 생각해야하고 그래서 그것을
turned out later that you actually don't need a surprise process you can just
실제로 깜짝 과정을 필요로하지 않는 것이 나중에 밝혀졌다 당신은 할 수 있습니다
trade with backdrop right away but you have to be very careful with
바로 배경으로 거래를하지만 당신은 매우 신중해야
initialization and they used signaling that works at this point and sigmoid are
초기화 및 그들은이 점과 시그 모이 있습니다에서 작동 신호를 사용
just not a great option to use and so basically backdrop works but you have to
그냥 좋은 옵션은 사용하지 그래서 기본적으로 배경은 작동하지만 당신은에 있습니다
be careful in how you use it and so this was in 2006 so a bit more research is
당신이 그것을 사용하는 방법에주의 등이 너무 좀 더 연구가 2006 년이었다
kind of came back to the area and was rebranded as deep learning but really
가지 다시 지역에 와서 깊은 학습으로하지만, 정말 재 상표되었다
it's still neural networks synonymous but it's a better word for the art and
여전히 신경망 동의어이다하지만 예술에 대한 더 나은 단어이고
basically at this point I think start to work properly well and people could
기본적으로 내가 생각하는이 시점에서 제대로 잘 작동하기 시작하고 사람들이 수
actually trained networks now still not too many people paid attention and when
실제로 훈련 네트워크는 지금 여전히 너무 많은없는 사람들이 관심을 때
people start to really pay attention was roughly I think around 2010 and 2012 so
사람들이 정말 관심이 내가 그렇게 2010 년과 2012 년의 주위에 생각하는 정도였다 지불 시작
specifically in 2010 there were two first really big result for neural
특히 2010 년 신경에 대한이 첫번째 정말 큰 결과가 있었다
networks really worked really well compared to everything else that you had
네트워크는 정말 당신이 한 다른 모든 것들에 비해 정말 잘했다
in your machine learning toolkit
당신의 기계 학습 툴킷
kernels or espionage and so on and this was specifically the speech recognition
커널 정도에 간첩과이 구체적으로 음성 인식했다
area where they took this GMM HMM framework and they swapped out long part
그들은이 GMM의 HMM 프레임 워크를했다 그들은 긴 부분을 스왑 영역
in sports network and Internet would give him huge improvements in 2010 and
스포츠 네트워크 및 인터넷에서 2010 년에 그에게 큰 개선을 줄 것이며,
this was worked on Microsoft and so people start to pay attention because
이 마이크로 소프트에 근무하고 그래서 사람들이 있기 때문에주의를 기울여야 시작
this was the first time that works really came from a large improvements
이건 정말 큰 개선에서 나온 작품이 처음이다
and then we saw that again in 2012 where he played out even more dramatically in
그는 더 극적으로 펼쳐 곳, 그리고, 우리는 2012 년에 다시 보았다
the domain of visual recognition and computer vision where basically we took
우리가했다 기본적으로 시각적 인식 및 컴퓨터 비전의 도메인
this 2012 network by all scratched D Anton and basically a crush the
모든 긁힌 D 안톤하여이 2012 네트워크와 기본적으로 호감
competition from all the features and there was a really large improvement
모든 기능에서 경쟁과 정말 큰 개선이 있었다
from these neural networks that we witnessed and that's what people really
이들 신경망에서 우리가 목격하고는 어떤 사람들이 정말
start to pay attention and since then the field this kind of exploded and
관심과 폭발의 다음 필드입니다 이런 종류의 지불 시작
there's a lot of area in this field now
이 필드 영역의 많은 지금 거기
and so will go into details I think a bit later in the possible why it started
그래서 그것을 시작하는 이유는 수에 조금 나중에 생각 세부 사항으로 이동합니다
to work early 2010
2010 초기 작동합니다
it's a combination of things but I think it's we've got to be figured out a
그것은 사물의 조합이다 그러나 나는 우리가 알아 낸 수있어 생각
better way to visualizing of getting these things to work of activation
활성화 작업에이 일을 얻는 시각화에 더 나은 방법
functions and we had GPUs and we have much more data and so really a lot of
기능과 우리의 GPU를 가지고 있었고, 우리는 그렇게 정말 훨씬 더 많은 데이터를 많이 가지고
the stuff before didn't quite work because it was just not there in terms
이 점에서 그냥 있었기 때문에 물건 전에 확실히 작동하지 않았다
of computer data and some of the ideas just tweaking and so that's rough
컴퓨터 데이터와 아이디어의 일부에 불과 조정 등 그 거친
historical setting so we basically went throughout over promising underdog over
역사적 그래서 우리는 기본적 통해 유망 약자 이상에 걸쳐 갔다
processing and delivery and now it seems like things are actually trying to work
처리 및 배달하고 지금은 일처럼 보인다는 실제로 작동하려고
really well and so that's where we are at this point
정말 잘 우리는이 시점에서 어디 그래서이다
ok I'm going to dive into the specifics and we'll see exactly will actually
확인 나는 세부 사항에 뛰어거야 그리고 우리는 정확히 것입니다 실제로 볼 수 있습니다
dying to know what works and how we train them properly so the overview of
작품을 알고 죽어가는 우리는의 개요 있도록 적절하게 훈련하는 방법
what we're going to cover over the course of the next year lectures is a
우리가 다음 해 강의의 과정을 통해 다루려고하는 것은 인
whole bunch of independent things so I'll just become peppering you with all
독립적 인 사물의 전체 무리 그래서 난 그냥 모든 당신을 peppering 될 수 있습니다
these little areas that we have to understand and see what people do in the
우리가 이해하고 사람들이에서 무엇을 볼 수있는이 작은 지역
case and we'll go through them the pros and cons of all trades as how you
경우 우리는 그들을 통해 방법을 모든 거래의 장단점을 갈거야
actually properly trained neural networks and real-world datasets to the
실제로 제대로에 신경 네트워크와 실제 데이터 세트를 훈련
first thing we're going to talk about
먼저 우리가 얘기하는거야
activation functions as I promised I think a lecture so ago so is this
활성화 기능은 내가 강의 그래서 전 그렇게이 생각 약속
function at the top of their own and we saw that it can have many different
자신의 정상 기능에 우리는 다른 많은 수 보았다
phones so these are all different proposals for what these activation
이 때문에 휴대폰은 무엇 이러한 활성화에 대한 모든 다른 제안입니다
functions can look like they're going to go through some prison calls and how you
그들이 어떤 감옥 통화 및 방법을 통해 갈 것 같은 기능을 볼 수 있습니다
think about what an activation what are going to desirable properties of an
의 바람직한 특성에가는 무엇을 어떻게 활성화에 대해 생각
activation function so historically the one that has been used the most is the
활성화 기능을 가장 많이 사용 된 역사적으로 하나가 그래서
sigmoid nonlinearity which looks like this so it's basically squashing
그것은 기본적 부수 그래서 다음과 같습니다 시그 모이 드 비선형
function it takes a real value number
그것이 진정한 가치 번호를 취 기능
squashes it to be between 0 and one and so the first problem with the sigmoid is
그래서 시그 모이와 첫 번째 문제는 0과 1 사이 과즙은가되게합니다
that as was pointed out a few lectures to go there's a problem that saturated
지적 된 바와 같이 몇 가지 강의 포화 문제가 거기에 갈 것을
neurons which are either very close to zero or very close to one of those
어느 제로에 매우 가까이 또는 그 중 하나에 매우 가까운 뉴런
neurons kill gradients during back propagation and so I like to expand on
신경 세포는 다시 전파 동안 구배를 죽이고 그래서 난에 확장하려면
this entry exactly what this means and this contributes to something that we're
이 항목은 정확히 이것이 의미하는 어떤이는 우리가있어 뭔가에 기여
going to call the bench ingredient problem so let's look at the gate in the
벤치 성분 문제를 호출하려고하는 것은 그래서이의 게이트를 살펴 보자
back in the circuit and receive some
다시 회로의 일부를받을
and signal that comes out and then in back probably have deal by decent and we
그리고이 나오고 다시 아마 괜찮은 우리로 거래를 신호
like to back drop it through the second gate to using chain rule so that we have
우리가 가질 수 있도록 체인 규칙을 사용하여 제 2 게이트를 통해 드롭 백업하려면
a deal by Dax at the end and you can see that through chain rule basically told
당신이 체인 규칙을 통해 그것을 볼 수있는 끝에서 닥스에 의한 거래는 기본적으로 말했다
us to multiply those two quantities and so think about what happens when this
우리는이 두 수량을 곱 등 때 일어나는 일에 대해 생각하는
signaled gate receives and put off by 10 or 20 or 10 it competes in value and
신호 게이트 받아 10 또는 20 또는 가치가 경쟁 (10)에 의해 연기
then it's getting some gradient from the top and what happens to that radiant as
다음은 정상에서 약간의 그라데이션을지고있어 무엇은 그 방사에 미치는 영향
your backdrop through the circuit in any of these cases where is that possible
이러한 경우 중 하나의 회로를 통해 배경이 가능한 것입니다
problem in some of these cases so so you're saying that the gradient is very
당신은 그라데이션이 매우이라고 말을하는지 그래서, 그래서이 경우 일부에서 문제
low when Texas negative 10 or 10 and wait to see this is basically we have
텍사스 마이너스 10 또는 10이 기본적으로 우리가 있습니다보고 기다릴 때 낮은
this local gradient here that will be multiplying with this gradient this
이 그라데이션 곱됩니다 여기에이 지역의 그라데이션이
local gradient defund the DOMA bydy X when you're at the negative 10 you can
당신은 당신이 할 수있는 네거티브 (10)에있을 때 현지 구배 X bydy DOMA를 defund
see that the gradient is basically zero because the slope at this point zero and
그래디언트 기본적 제로임을 알 때문에이 때의 기울기 제로
gradient attend will also be near zero and so the issue is that you're reading
그라데이션 참석도 제로 근처에있을 것입니다 그래서 문제는 당신이 읽고있는 것입니다
will drop in from here but if you're on the saturated so it basically it 0 had
여기에서 드롭하지만 당신은에있어 경우는 그래서 기본적으로 0이 있었다 포화됩니다
it won then the gradient will be killed
그 다음 원 그라데이션 살해한다
I'll just be multiplied by a very tiny number and great info will stop through
난 그냥 아주 작은 수를 곱한됩니다 큰 정보를 통해 중지
them through the signature on so you can imagine if you have a large network of
당신의 대규모 네트워크가있는 경우의 서명을 통해 그들 그래서 당신은 상상할 수
sigmoid neurons and many of them are in a saturated regime where they're either
시그 모이 신경 세포와 그들 중 많은 사람들이 하나있어 포화 정권에
0 or 1 ingredients can't back propagate through the network because they'll be
그들이 될 것이기 때문에 0 또는 1 성분은 다시 네트워크를 통해 전파 할 수 없습니다
stopped if you're sitting in your office or in the saturated or jeans ingredients
당신이 당신의 사무실 또는 포화 또는 청바지 성분에 앉아하는 경우 중지
only flow if you're kind of in a safer zone and what we call an active region
단지 당신이 있다면 안전한 영역에 종류의 흐름과 우리는 활성 영역은 무엇 전화
of the sigmoid and so that's kind of a problem we'll see more about this soon
S 상과 그래서 문제의 종류 우리는이에 대한 자세한 내용을 곧 볼 수 있어요
another problem with the sigmoid is that there are not zero centered so we'll
시그 모이 또 다른 문제는 우리가 거​​ 야가 중심 제로되지 않은 것입니다
talk about the preprocessing soon but you always want to when you process your
당신이 처리 할 때 곧 전처리에 대해 이야기하지만 당신은 항상하려는
day want to make sure that it's zero centered right and in this case is
이 경우는에 하루는 제로 중심으로 오른쪽의이 있는지 확인하려면 및
supposed to have a big network of several layers of sigmund their opening
지그문트 자신의 개구부의 여러 레이어의 큰 네트워크를 가지고 가정
these 90 centered values between 0 and one and we're putting more basically
0과 1 사이이 (90)을 중심으로 값은 우리가 더 기본적으로 퍼팅하는
leader classifiers that were stacked on top of each other
서로의 상부에 적층 리더 분류
and the problem roughly with non-zero centered up but I'll just try to give
그리고 약 비 - 제로의 문제는 최대 중심하지만 난 그냥 포기하려고합니다
you a bit of an intuition on what goes wrong
당신이 잘못되면 무엇에 직관의 비트
concern Iran that computes this function right 0 to 60 in Iran looking at just
그냥보고이란 바로 공 (60)이 함수를 계산 관심이란
competing W must be and what can we say about think about what you can say about
W 경쟁은해야하고 우리는 당신에 대해 말할 수있는 생각에 대해 무슨 말을 할 수 있습니다
the gradients on W during backpropagation if your exes are all
역 전파시 W의 기울기는 예전 친구는 모든 경우
positive in this case between 011 so maybe you're in Iran somewhere deep in
011 사이의 경우 긍정적 어쩌면 당신은 어딘가 깊은이란에있어
the network what can you say about the weights if all the excess are positive
모든 초과가 긍정적 인 경우 네트워크는 당신이 무게에 대해 무엇을 말할 수있다
numbers
번호
constrained in a way ahead on the green WR either a positive or negative and
녹색 WR에 앞서 방법으로 제한하거나 양 또는 음과
that is because gradient flows in from the top and if you think about the
그라데이션 상단에서 유입 때문이고, 당신이 생각하는 경우
expression for all the W radiance they're basically X times the gradient
모든 W의 광채에 대한 표현들이있어 기본적으로 X 시간 그라데이션
and so the gradient off on the upper of the neuron is positive then all your W
그래서 신경 세포의 상단에 그라데이션 오프는 모든 W 긍정적이다
gratings will be positive and vice versa so basically you end up at this case
격자는 긍정적 것이며, 그 반대의 경우도 마찬가지 그래서 기본적으로 당신이 경우에 결국
where it's supposed to have just two weights so you have the first wait a
첫 번째 대기 a를 그래서 두 가중치를 했어야 어디
second wait what ends up happening is other ingredients for that for that as
둘째 무슨 일이 끝나는 것은으로 그것에 대해 그 다른 성분 인 대기
this goes through your computer ready in the weights there either positive or
이 거기에 무게에서 컴퓨터를 통해 준비가 진행 중 긍정적 또는
negative and so the issue is that your constrained and the kind of update you
음 그래서 문제는이 제한되어 있고 업데이트의 종류의
can make and you end up with this undesirables exacting path if you want
하고 당신이 원하는 경우 경로를 엄격한이 바람직하지 않은 끝낼 수 있습니다
to get to some parts that are outside of these regions this kind of like a
유사한 이런 종류의이 지역 이외의 몇 가지 부분에 도착합니다
slightly henry VIII reason here but just to give you intuition and you can see
약간 헨리 VIII 이유 여기지만 단지는 직관주고 당신은 볼 수 있습니다
this empirically when you train with things that are not zero centered you
이 경험적으로 당신은 영을 중앙에 있지 것들로 훈련 할 때
observed slower convergence and this is a bit of a hand with a reason for why
느린 수렴을 관찰하고이 이유에 대한 이유와 손의 비트입니다
that might happen but I think if you actually want to go much deeper into
그런 일이 있습니다하지만 난 당신이 실제로으로 훨씬 더 깊게 할 경우 생각
that you can and there are people talking about this but you have to then
당신이 말하는 사람들이있다 할 수 있지만 다음에 있는지
reason about mathematics official major season natural gradients and gets a bit
수학 공식의 주요 계절 자연 그라디언트에 대한 이유와는 조금 얻는다
more complex than this but i just wanted to give you intuition for you want to
더 이것보다 복잡하지만 난 그냥 당신이 원하는 당신의 직관을주고 싶어
have zero Center things in the input you want to have their santa thing
당신이 그들의 산타 일을하려는 입력에 제로 센터 일들이
throughout the white thinks things as nicely and so that is a downside of
흰색은 멋지게 일을 생각하고 그래서 그의 단점 인을 통해
signaling their own and the last one is that XP function inside this expression
이 식 내부 XP 해당 함수는 자신의 마지막 하나되는 시그널링
is kind of expensive to compute compared to some of the alternatives of other
기타의 대안 중 일부에 비해 계산하는 종류의 비용이
charities and so it's just a small detail I suppose when you actually
자선 단체 그래서 그냥 작은 세부 사항의 난 때를 실제로 가정
trained these large commercial networks most of the computer time isn't
이러한 큰 상업 네트워크를 훈련 컴퓨터가 대부분의 시간은 아니다
competitions and these dot product it's not in this expiration and so it's kind
대회 이러한 내적는이 만료에없는 등 그 종류의
of banishing small contribution but it's still something that is a bit of a
작은 기여를 추방하지만 아직도 조금 무언가이다
downside compared to the other parts so I'm going to ask if you think a few
난 당신이 몇 가지를 생각하면 물어 갈거야, 그래서 다른 부분에 비해 단점
questions so tender age is an attempt to fix one of these problems in particular
어린 나이 때문에 질문은 특히 이러한 문제를 해결하기 위해 시도이다
the fact that it's 90 centered so eloquent in 1991 right wrote a very nice
그것은 1991 년에 이렇게 웅변을 중심으로 90 년대 있다는 사실은 바로 아주 좋은 썼다
paper on how you optimize your network
네트워크를 최적화하는 방법에 대한 논문
and I links to it from the syllabus and he recommended that people use any extra
그리고 나는 강의에서에 연결하고 그 사람들이 어떤 여분을 사용하는 것이 좋습니다
steps intended to affect basically is kind of like two segments but together
기본적으로 영향을위한 단계의 두 세그먼트하지만 함께 같은 종류의
you end up with being between negative one and one and so you're up with 40
당신은 당신이 (40)과 함께있어 음 하나 하나 너무 사이에있는와 끝까지
centered but otherwise you have still up something from the other problems like
중심하지만 그렇지 않으면 같은 다른 문제에서 무언가까지 여전히이
for example you have these regions where if you get saturated no gradients flow
예를 들어, 당신은 당신이 포화받을 경우이 지역 그라디언트 흐름 없음을
and so we haven't really fix that at this point but so many just I think
그래서 우리가 정말이 시점에서 그 문제를 해결하지 않은하지만 너무 많은 그냥 생각
strictly prefer to sigmoid because it has all the same problems except for 10
엄밀하게는 (10)을 제외한 모든 같은 문제가 있기 때문에 S 자형 선호
continue and then maybe we can take more questions so around 2012 in the paper by
계속 어쩌면 우리가 신문에 그렇게 2012 주위에 더 많은 질문을 할 수 있습니다
Oscar Jessica this is the first commercial networks paper we propose
오스카 제시카 이것은 우리가 제안하는 최초의 상용 네트워크 종이입니다
that actually we noticed that this nonlinearity where you use maxis Iran X
실제로 우리는 발견 당신이 맥 시스이란 X를 사용하여이 비선형
instead of sigmoid or 10 each
대신에 S 자형 또는 10 각의
just make sure networks converter much quicker and in their experiments almost
단지 훨씬 빠르고 자신의 실험을 거의에서 확인 네트워크 변환을
my height of 6 and so we can go back and try to think about why is this and what
제 6의 높이와 우리가 돌​​아가서 이유에 대해 생각하는 시도 할 수 있습니다이 무엇 인
kind of reading into it like you can see that it works better in practice but
종류의 당신이 실제로 잘 작동하는지 볼 수있는 것처럼 그것으로 읽고 있지만,
explaining it does not always as easy to hear some reason is hoping for a while
항상 쉬운 몇 가지 이유를 듣고 있지 않는 것을 설명하는 것은 잠시 동안 기대
people are thinking that this works much better so one thing is that this this
사람들은 그래서 한 가지이이 있다는 것입니다이 훨씬 더 잘 작동하는지 생각
role in your own and does not sanctuary at least a positive region so at least
자신의 역할과 적어도 그렇게 성소하지 적어도 긍정적 인 영역
in this region you don't have the Spanish ingredient problem where your
여기서,이 지역에서 당신은 스페인 성분 문제가없는 당신의
brilliance will just kind of died and you have this issue where the neurons
광택은 종류의 사망하고이 문제가 어디 뉴런이
are only active in a small area that is bounded from both sides but these
양측하지만 이들로부터 경계하는 작은 영역 만 활성화됩니다
neurons actually active in a sense of the back propagate correctly or not
뒷면의 의미에서 실제로 활성 뉴런이 제대로 여부를 전파
correctly but at least they don't like 80 oz at least half of their regions
올바르게 그러나 적어도 그들은 그들의 지역의 80온스 절반 이상을 좋아하지 않는다
they're much more computationally efficient you're just holding and
그들이있어 훨씬 더 그냥 잡고있어 효율적으로 계산하고
experimental you can see that this number just so much much faster so this
실험 당신은이 숫자를 너무 많이 더 빨리 그래서이를 볼 수 있습니다
is called the rela- near on the file in your unit was pointed out in this paper
근처 누린다 당신의 장치에있는 파일에 대한 호출은이 논문에서 지적했다
for the first time that this works much better and this is kind of like a
이 훨씬 더 잘 작동이이 같은 종류의 것을 처음으로
detailed recommendations what you should use at this point at the same time there
자세한 권장 사항은 무엇가 동시에이 시점에서 사용한다
are several problems with this ruling Iran so one thing again notice that it's
이 판결이란 그래서 한 가지 몇 가지 문제가 다시 그것의 것을 알 수 있습니다
not zero centered up it's so not completely ideal perhaps and a slight
하지 제로는 그렇게 완전히 아마도 이상과 약간 아니다 업을 중심으로
annoyance of the ruling Iran
집권이란의 성가심
that we can talk about it and think about is what happens when there's
이 때 발생하는 무엇에 대해 우리는 그것에 대해 이야기하고 생각할 수 있음
really no 10 what happens during the propagation if Iran does not become
정말 전파 진행 상황에 대해 더 (10)는이란이 될하지 않는 경우
active in the forecast stays in active thundering backdrop what they do it
예측에 적극적으로 그들이 그것을 무엇을 활성 천둥 배경에 남아
kills right that kills the gradient and so the way to see this of course is that
물론이 있다는 것입니다의 그라데이션 등 방법을 죽이는 권리를 확인하기 죽이기
when the same picture and if you read too negative say 10 than your local
때 너무 부정적인 읽을 경우 동일한 그림이 현지보다 10 말과
gradient here will just be zero because there's no there's just zero gradient
이 때문에 더 그냥 제로 그라데이션이 그냥 0이됩니다 여기에 그라데이션
identically it's not just you squish degrading down you actually kill it
동일 그것은 단지 당신이 그것을 죽일 실제로 당신을 저하 뭉개 버려 아니에요
completely so anyone that does not activate will not that propagate
완전히 그렇게 작동하지 않는 사람은 그 전파되지 않습니다
downwards its weights will not be updated and nothing happens below it at
아래의 무게가 업데이트 아무것도에서 그 아래에 발생하지 않습니다
least for its contribution and a tactic was ten was the local gradient that's
기여와 전술에 대한 최소한 10입니다 지역 그라데이션이었다
just one so just passes through gradients just a gate if if if if its
하나는, 그래서 그냥 그라데이션을 통해 단지 게이트를 통과 할 경우 경우 경우 경우의
assets out that was positive and then it just passing reading through otherwise
그 밖의 자산은 긍정적하고 그냥 통과 그렇지 통해 읽기
it kills a kind of like a great game to date and by the way what happens when
그것은 지금까지 좋은 게임 같은 종류의를 죽이고 그런데 무슨 일이 때 발생
Texas 0 what is your gradient at that point it's actually undefined that's
실제로 그건 정의되지 않은 것 그 시점에서 당신의 그라데이션을 손쉽게 텍사스 0
right the green does not exist at that point we only talked about whenever I
오른쪽 녹색은 우리가 단지 내가 할 때마다 이야기 그 시점에서 존재하지 않는
talk about gradient just assumed that I always mean some gradient which is a
그라데이션에 대한 이야기​​는 내가 항상 일부 기울기를 의미하는 것으로 가정
generalization of gradient two functions that are sometimes not differentiable to
때때로에 미분없는 그라데이션이 기능의 일반화
hear the limit does not exist but there's a whole bunch of some gradients
존재하지 않는 한계를들을 수 있지만, 일부 그라디언트의 전체 무리가있다
that could be 0 or 1 and so that's what we use usually in practice this
즉, 0 또는 1이 될 수 있고 그래서 우리가 연습이 보통 사용하는 무엇을
distinction doesn't really matter too much but i wanna talk about the south in
차이는 너무 많은 정말 중요하지 않습니다하지만 난에서 남쪽에 대해 이야기를하고 싶어
the case of by miramax Kate X&Y and someone asked the question what happens
무슨 미라 케이트 X & Y 누군가에 의해의 경우는 질문을
if X&Y are equal then that case you you can also have a kink in the function and
X & Y가 동일한 경우 그 경우 당신은 또한 기능에 꼬임을 가질 수 있으며,
makes them vulnerable but in practice these things don't really matter just
그들 취약하게하지만 실제로 이런 일들은 정말 상관 없어
pick one so you can have a great in 2011 there and things will work just fine and
하나를 선택 그래서 당신이 2011 년에 큰를 가질 수 있고, 일이 잘 작동하고
that's roughly because these are very unlikely cases that you end up right
이 당신이 권리를 결국 매우 않을 경우이기 때문에 그 약이다
there
그곳에
ok so the issue with relo roughly here's the problem that happens in practice he
확인 그래서 RELO의 문제는 대략 여기에 실제로 발생하는 문제입니다 그
tried to Israel units and one thing that you have to be aware of is you have
당신은 당신이 인의 알고 있어야 이스라엘 단위와 한 가지로 시도
these neurons that if they don't put anything they won't get any great dental
그들은 아무것도 넣지 않는 경우, 어떤 좋은 치과를 얻을하지 않습니다 이러한 뉴런
kill it
죽여
update and so what's the issue is supposed to have something happen is
업데이트 등 문제가있을 것으로 예상되는 무슨 뭔가 일이
when you initialize you're really neurons you can initialize them in a non
당신이있어 초기화 할 때 정말 당신이 비에를 초기화 할 수 있습니다 뉴런
not very lucky way and what ends up happening is suppose this is your guide
아니 아주 운이 방법은 어떤 생각되는 일이 끝이 당신의 가이드
a cloud of inputs to your Eleanor owns four you can end up with is what we call
당신의 엘레 노어의 입력의 구름은 우리가 부르는 끝낼 수있는 네 소유
a dead relative a dead ringer on so if this neuron only activates in the region
이 신경 세포는 지역의 활성화 경우 등 죽은 상대 죽은 벨소리
outside of your data cloud in this bed trailer will never become activated and
이 침대 트레일러에서 데이터 클라우드의 외부가 활성화 될하지 않습니다 및
then it will never update and so this can happen in one of two ways either
다음은 업데이트하지 않습니다 때문에이 중 두 가지 방법 중 하나를 발생할 수 있습니다
during initialization you were really really unlucky and you happen to sample
초기화하는 동안 당신은 정말 운이 있었고, 당신은 샘플 일
waits for her role in your own in such a way that that neuron will never turn on
그 신경이 켜지지 않을 것입니다 그런 방법으로 자신의 그녀의 역할을 기다립니다
in that case in Iran will not rain but more often what happens is during
이란이 경우 비가되지 않지만 더 자주 발생하는 중입니다
training if you are learning rate is high then think about these neurons ask
당신이 속도를 학습하는 경우 훈련은 이러한 뉴런 요청에 대해 생각 높다
around and we can happen sometimes by chance they just got knocked off the
우리는 기회가 종종 발생할 수 있습니다 주위에 그리고 그들은 단지 떨어져 기절있어
data manifold and when that happens then they will never get activated again and
데이터 매니 폴드와 그 다음 일어날 때 그들은 다시 활성화하지 않고 얻을 않을 것
they will not come back to the data manifold and you can see there's
그들은 데이터 매니 폴드에 다시 오지 않을 당신은 거기에 볼 수 있습니다
actually practice like sometimes you can train a big neural net with delegates
실제로 때때로 당신이 대표단에 큰 신경 그물을 훈련 할 수처럼 연습
and you try it and it seems to work fine and then what you do you stop the
당신은 그것을 시도하고 그것을 잘 작동하는 것 같다 다음 당신이를 중지 할 것
training and you pass your entire training dataset through your network
교육 당신은 당신의 네트워크를 통해 전체 훈련 데이터 세트를 전달
and you look at the statistics of every single neuron and what can happen is
당신은 모든 단일 신경 세포의 통계를 보면 어떤 일어날 수있는 것은
that as much as like 10 or 20 percent of your network is dead
네트워크의만큼 10 등, 20 %가 죽었다는
designer on that never turned on for anything in the training data and this
그에 디자이너는 훈련 데이터의 어떤이에 대해 설정되지 않습니다
could actually happen usually it's because you're learning rate was high
실제로 당신이 비율이 높았다 배우고 있기 때문이다 일반적으로 일어날 수
and so those are just like dead parts of your network and you can call pataki
그래서 사람들은 네트워크의 죽은 부분처럼 당신은 파타키를 호출 할 수 있습니다
schemes for real nationalizing these things and so on
실제 등등 이러한 것들과 국유화에 대한 계획
people don't usually do it as much but it's something to be aware of and it's a
사람들은 일반적으로 많이하지 않습니다하지만주의해야 할 뭔가 그리고 그것은이다
problem with this nonlinearity and so especially for initialization because of
이 비선형으로 그래서 특히 때문에 초기화 문제
this dead real problem with people like to do is normally initialize the bus 10
사람이 죽은 진짜 문제는 일반적으로 버스를 초기화하면된다 좋아 (10)
instead people in this life was slightly positive numbers Lexi 0101 because that
이 생활에있는 사람들이 그 때문에 렉시 0101 약간 양수이었다 대신
makes it more likely that an initialisation these roman numbers and
수 그것은 가능성이 있음을 초기화 이러한 로마 숫자와
old will get updates so it makes it less likely that the neuron will just never
그것은 덜 것을 수 있도록 이전 업데이트를 얻을 것이다 신경 단지 않습니다
become activated ever throughout training but I don't actually I think
교육을 통해 지금까지 활성화 될하지만 난 생각 실제로하지 않습니다
this is likely have a controversial point out some people claim that
이 가능성이 논쟁 점을 가지고있다 어떤 사람들은 주장
help sexy some people say that it actually doesn't help at all and so just
어떤 사람들은 실제로 모든 그래서 그냥 도움이되지 않는 말 섹시 도움
something to think about any questions at this point we are going to go into
뭔가 우리가 들어갈 예정이 시점에서 질문에 대해 생각하는
some other wants ok so let's look at things like people trying to fix a loose
다른 지금의 사람들이 느슨한를 해결하기 위해 노력 같은 것들을 살펴 보자 확인 원
so one issue with relatives as these dead neurons are not ideal so here's one
이러한 죽은 신경 세포가 아니기 때문에 그래서 친척 하나의 문제는, 그래서 여기에 하나를 이상적
proposal which is called the leaky rain and the idea of leaking really is
누설 비와 정말 누출의 아이디어라고 제안
basically we want this kink and we want this peace finally RT and we want the
기본적으로 우리는이 꼬임을 원하고 우리는이 평화 마침내 RT 원하는 우리가 원하는
sufficiency of but the issue is that in these this region your dreams die so
하지만 문제의 자족이 지역이 당신의 꿈이 너무 죽을 것입니다
instead let's make this slightly negatively sloped here or slightly
대신의 약간 부정적으로 여기거나 약간 경 사진이를 만들어 보자
positively sloped I suppose in this region and so you end up with this
긍정적으로 나는이 지역에서 가정 경사 등이와 끝까지
function and that's called a leaky and so some people are people showing that
기능과 그가 새는 그래서 어떤 사람들은 사람들이 있음을 보여주고있다라는 것
this works slightly better you don't have this issue of neurons dying but I
이것은 당신이 죽어가는 신경이 문제가 있지만하지 않는 약간 더 나은 작품
think it's not completely established that this works always better and then
완전히이 항상 더 나은 다음 작동 설정되지 않은 생각
some people playing with this even more so right now this is your apt 101 but
이 가지고 노는 어떤 사람들은 더욱 더 지금이 당신의 아파트 101 만
that can actually be an arbitrary parameter and then you get something
그 사실은 임의의 매개 변수가 될 수 있으며, 당신은 뭔가를 얻을
that's called a parametric rectifier or people who and basically the idea here
그는 파라 메트릭 정류기 또는 사람과 여기에 기본적으로 아이디어라고
is to introduce this is 101 which is a parameter in your network and this can
이 네트워크의 매개 변수를 101 인이 할 수있는 소개한다
be learned you can back up to get into it and so these neurons basically can
배울 당신은 그것으로 얻을 백업 할 수 있습니다 그래서 이러한 뉴런은 기본적으로 수
choose what slope to have in his native region ok and so they can become
확인 자신의 고유 영역이 무엇을 사면 선택하고 그래서 그들은 될 수 있습니다
irrelevant if they want to or they can become a leak or they can be they have
그들이 원하는 또는 그들이 누출 될 수 있습니다 또는 그들이 가질 수 있습니다 관련성이없는 경우
the choice roughly every neuron is this the kind of things that people play with
선택은 거의 모든 신경이 사람들이 노는 물건의 종류
when they tried to design a good day too in just a very normal way your
그들은 단지 매우 일반적인 방법으로 너무 좋은 일을 설계하려 할 때
competition go out there every neuron will have its just like it has its own
그것은 그것의 자신의 그 것처럼 경쟁은 모든 신경 세포가있을 것이다 나가서
bias
바이어스
go ahead
진행
I'll finds one then you're going to get an identity so that's probably not
나는거야 그건 아마 그래서 한 다음 ID를받을거야 발견
something that the propagation will want in a sense that if that wasn't identity
전파는 의미에서 원하는 무언가 그 정체성 아니었다면 그
then that shouldn't be very competition a useful so you might expect that baby
당신이 아기를 예상 할 수 있도록 그 아주 경쟁에게 유용한이어야한다
back propagation should not actually get you to those regions of the space and
다시 전파가 실제로 공간이 그 지역에 당신을 얻을 안되며,
maybe even perhaps I don't actually think if I remember correctly there is
내가 제대로이 기억한다면 어쩌면 아마도 내가 실제로 생각하지 않습니다
no specific things where people really worried about that too much but I could
특별한 일없는 곳에 너무 많이하지만 내가 할 수있는 것을 정말 걱정 명
be wrong ahead I read the paper while ago now and I don't use these too much
잘못된 앞으로있을 이제 얼마 전 신문을 읽고 나는이 너무 많이 사용하지 않는
work and then so one issue still is as we saw it so these are different schemes
작동하고 그래서 하나의 문제는 여전히 우리가 그것을보고 이러한 서로 다른 방식이있다
for fixing the bed railing Iran's there's another people that only came
이란의 난간 침대를 고정하는 경우에만 온 다른 사람들이있다
out for example roughly two months ago so this just gives you a sense of how
약 두 달 전, 예를 들면 밖으로 그래서 이것은 당신에게 방법의 감각을 준다
new this field is there are papers coming out just two months ago trying to
논문하려고 두 달 전에 새로운이 필드는이 나오고있다
propose a new activation functions one of them is exponential in your units are
하여 단위 중 하나를 지수로하는 새로운 기능을 활성화가 제안
just give you an idea about what people play with it tries to have all the
이 모든이 시도에 당신에게 사람들이 즐기는 게임에 대한 아이디어를 제공
benefits of relew buttressed to get rid of this downside of being non-zero
힘 입어 relew의 장점 인 비 - 제로의 이러한 단점을 없애
centered and so they end up with is this blue function here that looks like a
중심 그래서 그들은처럼 보이는 여기 푸른 함수와 끝까지
real issue but in the negative region it doesn't just go to zero or doesn't just
진짜 문제 만은 음의 영역에 그냥 제로에 갈하거나하지 않습니다 않습니다
go down as a leak but it has this funny shape and there are two pages of math in
누수로 내려가하지만이 재미있는 모양을 가지고 있으며, 수학의 두 페이지에 있습니다
the paper
종이
justifying partly why you want that and roughly when you do this end up with
부분적으로 정당화 당신은 원하는 이유는 대략 당신과 함께이 말을 할 때
zero mean outlets and they claim that the strains better and I think there's
제로 평균 아울렛 그리고 그들은 그 균주 더 나은 주장 내가 있다고 생각
some controversy about this and so we're basically trying to figure all of this
어떤이에 대한 논쟁과 우리는 기본적으로이 모든 것을 이해하려고 노력하고 있습니다
out
아웃
active area of research and we're not sure what to do yet but rather is right
활성 연구의 영역과 우리가 오히려 아직 어떻게해야할지 확실하지 않다하지만 권리
now are like a safe recommendation if you if you're careful with it so that's
당신이 조심 있다면 당신은 그 그래서 경우 ​​지금 안전 권고처럼
a loose and one more I would like to note mention because it's relatively
느슨한 하나 상대적이기 때문에 내가 언급을 주목하고 싶습니다 더
common in you'll see it if you read about it works is this max out their own
일반적으로 당신이 작동에 대한 것은 자신의 출력이 최대입니다 읽으면 당신은 그것을 볼에
from hotel and basically it's a very different from iran it's not just an
호텔에서 기본적으로는이란에서 매우 다른있어 그것을 그냥 아니에요
activation function that looks different
다른 보이는 활성화 함수
it actually changes within Iran computer how computes doesn't just have this form
실제로 계산해 그냥이 양식이없는 방법이란 컴퓨터 내에서 변경
of W X it actually has two weights and then compute smacks of W transpose Xbox
WX의 실제로 두 개의 무게가 다음 W 난다는 X 박스를 바꾸어 계산
be another set of WSYX must be the end up with these like to hike a place that
이러한 장소를 하이킹을 좋아하여 WSYX의 또 다른 세트가 끝을 위로해야 할 그
you take a max over and that's what the near a computer
당신은을 통해 최대를 가지고 그건 컴퓨터 근처에 무엇을
you can see that there are many ways of playing with these activation functions
이러한 활성 기능을 가지고 노는 여러 가지 방법이 있다는 것을 볼 수있다
so this doesn't have some of the downsides of this want to die and it
그래서 이것은 이것의 단점 중 일부는 죽고 싶어해야하고하지 않습니다
still piecewise linear it's still efficient but not every single neuron
여전히 구분 선형은 여전히​​ 효율적인하지만 하나 하나 신경 세포의
has two weights and so you kind of double the number of parameters premiere
이 가중치를 가지고 있으며, 그래서 당신은 가지 매개 변수 초연의 수를 두 배로
on and so maybe that's not as ideal so some people use this but I think it's
그래서 아마 그 이상적인 아니에요에 그래서 어떤 사람들은 이것을 사용하지만 난 그게 생각
it's not super common I would say that roads are still most common
그것은 내가 도로가 여전히 가장 일반적인 것을 말할 것입니다 슈퍼 공통 아니다
into those winds will be different and so you end up a different weights for
그 바람에 상이 할 수 있고, 그래서 당신은 다른 가중치를 종료합니다
sure it's complicated it's complicated
확실히 복잡 복잡
is a lot of the optimization process is not just about the loss function but
최적화 프로세스의 많은 단지 손실 함수에 대한되지 않지만
just like about the dynamics of the backward flow of greens and we'll see a
다만 채소의 역류의 역학에 대해 좋아하고 우리는 표시됩니다
bit about that in next week's lies you have to really think about it
다음 주에 그것에 대해 조금 당신이 정말로 그것에 대해 생각할 필요가있다
dynamically more than just lost landscape and how it's so it's too
단지 잃어버린 풍경보다 동적으로 더 그렇게 너무 야 어떻게
complex and also you specifically stochastic gradient descent and has a
복잡하고 또한 특별히 확률 그라데이션 하강하고있다
particular form and something splaine nicer some liberties play nicely with
일부 자유가 멋지게 연주 좋네요 특정 형태와 뭔가 splaine
the fact that the optimization is tied the update is tied into all this as well
최적화 업데이트를 연결되어 있다는 사실뿐만 아니라 모든이에 연결되어
as kind of all interacting together and the choice of these activation functions
모두가 함께 상호 작용의 유형 및 이러한 활성 기능의 선택과 같은
and the choice of your updates are kind of coupled and it's very unclear when
및 업데이트의 선택은 종류의 결합이 때 매우 불분명하고 있습니다
you actually optimizes kind of complex think so while they are here is that you
그들이 여기있는 동안이다, 그래서 당신은 실제로 복잡한 생각의 종류를 최적화
can try out these guys you can try out anybody should expect too much I don't
이 녀석을 시도 할 수 있습니다 당신은 사람이 그렇게하지 ​​너무 많은 기대한다 시도 할 수
think people use it too much right now and don't ignore it because basically
사람들이 너무 많은 지금 사용하고 무시하지 않는 생각 기본적으로 인해
ten I just strictly better and you won't see people using voice now anymore
열 난 그냥 엄격하게 더 나은 당신은 사람들이 이제 더 이상 음성을 사용하여 볼 수 없습니다
of course we use it and things like long short term memory units palestinian
물론 우리는 긴 단기 기억 단위 팔레스타인 등을 사용
someone will go into that in a bit in recurrent neural networks but their
누군가가 재발 신경망하지만 자신의 비트에 해당로 이동합니다
specific reasons why we use them there and that will see later in class and
우리가 그들을 사용하고 수업 시간에 나중에 볼 이​​유 구체적인 이유와
they are they're used differently than what we've covered so far in like this
그들은 우리가 같이 멀리에 너무 커버 한 내용과 다르게 사용하는 것입니다
just fully connected sandwich makers multiply party and someone just having a
그냥 완전히 연결 샌드위치 메이커 파티를 곱 누군가 단지를 갖는
basic neural network oK so that's everything I wanted to say but
기본 신경망 확인 그게 내가 말하고 싶어 모든 그래서하지만
activation functions as basically this one had primary functions that we worry
활성화 기능은 기본적으로 이것을 우리가 걱정 주요 기능을했다
about this research about it and we haven't fully figured it out and there's
그것에 대해 본 연구에 대해 우리는 완전하게 파악하고있다하지 않은
some pros and cons and many of them come down to thinking about how the gradient
그들 중 많은 몇 가지 장점과 단점 및 방법 그라데이션에 대해 생각에 내려와
flows through your network and discuss these issues like dead relatives and yet
네트워크를 통해 흐르는 아직 죽은 친척과 같은 이러한 문제를 논의
to really know about the gradient flow if you try to debug your networks
당신이 당신의 네트워크를 디버깅하려고하면 정말 그라데이션 흐름에 대해 알아야 할 사항
and a to understand what's going on let's look at a price
그리고는 가격에하자 모습에 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는지 이해하기
processing very briefly so
처리 매우 간단하므로
processing just very briefly normally suppose you just have a cloud of
처리는 매우 간단 일반적으로 그냥 구름이 있다고 가정
original data and two dimensions here very common 20 Center your data so that
원래의 데이터와 여기에 두 가지 차원 (20) 센터 데이터 있도록 매우 일반적인
just means that along every single picture was to track the mean people
그냥 하나 하나 그림이었다 함께 평균 사람들을 추적 할 수 있음을 의미합니다
sometimes also when you go through machine learning literature try to
당신은 기계 학습 문학을 통해 갈 때 때때로 시도
normalize the data so in every single dimension you normalize say by standard
표준이 말을 당신이 정상화 모든 단일 차원 있도록 데이터를 정상화
deviation
일탈
standardizing are you can make sure that the min and max are within and so on
표준화는 최소 및 최대 내에 등등 있는지 확인 할 수 있습니다
there are several schemes for doing so in images it's not as common because you
이미지에 이렇게 여러 가지 방식이 거기 있기 때문에 일반적인 아니에요 있습니다
don't have to separate different features that can be a different units
다른 단위가 될 수있는 다양한 기능을 분리 할 필요가 없습니다
everything is just pixels and their own boundary between 0 and 255 it's not as
모든 것이 픽셀과 자신의 경계가로 아니라 0과 255
common to normalize the data but it's very common 20 Center your data you can
공통 데이터를 정상화하지만 당신이 할 수있는 매우 일반적인 20 센터 데이터의합니다
go further
더 나아가
normally in machine learning you can go ahead and your data has some covariance
일반적으로 시스템에서 당신이 앞서 갈 수있는 학습 데이터가 일부 공분산이
structure by default you can go ahead and make that communist Russia be
기본적으로 구조가 가서 그 공산주의 러시아 될 수 있습니다
diagonal say for example by applying PCA or you can go even further and you can
대각선은 PCA를 적용하여, 예를 들어 말을하거나 더도 갈 수 있고, 당신이 할 수있는
wipe your data and what that means is you kind of even squish after primed PCR
데이터를 닦아 무엇을 뜻하면 가지도 끝났다 PCR 후 뭉개 버려이다
you also squish your data so that your various metrics becomes just a diagonal
당신의 다양한 측정 그냥 대각선이되도록 당신은 또한 당신의 데이터를 뭉개 버려
and so that's another form of preprocessing I see people talk about it
그래서 그 사람들이 얘기 내가 볼 전처리의 또 다른 형태이다
and these are both I go much more detail in the class notes on BC I don't want to
이들은 모두 내가하지 않으려는 BC의 클래스 노트에서 더 자세한 내용을 갈 수 있습니다
go into too many details on that because it turns out that in images we don't
이 이미지에서 우리가하지 않는 것으로 나타났다 때문에 너무 많은 세부 사항으로 이동
actually end up using these even the order coming in machine learning
실제로 기계 학습오고 이러한에도 순서로 끝낸다
images specifically what's common is just a means centering and then a
이미지는 구체적으로 어떤 일반적인 것은 다음 단지 수단을 중심으로하고있다
particular variant of me centering that is slightly more convenient to practice
내가 그 중심의 특정 변종 연습 약간 더 편리합니다
so I mean centering we say 330 to buy three images subsea far if you want to
그래서 우리가 330 말을 중심으로 의미하는 것은 당신이 원하는까지하면 세 가지 이미지의 해저를 구입
center your data that for every single pixel you compete W overtraining such a
모든 단일 픽셀에 대해 당신이 오버 트레이닝 (W) 경쟁하는 것이 데이터를 중앙 등
track that out so what you end up with is this mean image that has basically
당신이 결국 그래서 그 무엇을 추적하는 것은 기본적으로 가지고이 평균 이미지
the mission of 32 by 32 by three so I think that mean image for example for
세에 의해 32로 32의 임무는 그래서 그 예에 대한 이미지를 의미 생각
image data justice orange blob tracking up from every single image to center
이미지 데이터 정의, 오렌지, 방울마다 하나의 이미지로부터 추적하는 것은 중앙에
your data to have better trained dynamics and one other form they're
데이터가 더 나은 훈련 역학과 그들이있어 하나의 다른 형태를 가질 수 있습니다
slightly more convenient is attracting just a per channel mean so you go into
약간 더 편리 단지 채널 당 그​​래서 당신이 들어갈 뜻 받고있다
red green and blue channel and computed the mean across all of space to just end
모든 공간은 단지 끝에서 적색, 녹색, 청색 채널의 평균을 계산
up with basically three numbers
기본적으로 세 개의 숫자 최대
moves in red green and blue channel and just a practice out and so some networks
적색, 녹색, 청색 채널의 이동 단지 연습 아웃 등 일부 네트워크
use that instead so those are two common skins this one is like a more convenient
사람들이 하나가 더 편리처럼 두 가지 일반적인 스킨입니다 대신 있도록 그 사용
because you only have to worry about those three numbers you don't have to
당신 만 걱정 세 개의 숫자를 가지고 있기 때문에 당신은 필요가 없습니다
worry about the giant array of mean that you have to ship around every writer
당신이 모든 작가를 주위에 제공 할 필요가 평균의 거대한 배열에 대해 걱정
when you're actually putting this up so not too much more I want to say about
당신은 실제로 너무 너무 많은 I에 대해 말하고 싶은이를 넣어 때
this just basically subtract the mean and computer vision applications things
이것은 단지 기본적으로 평균 및 컴퓨터 비전 응용 프로그램 일을 빼기
don't get much more complex than that in particular DPC and so on this used to be
특히 DPC에서보다 훨씬 더 복잡 얻을 등이에로 사용하지 않습니다
slightly common issues you can't apply to all images because your images are
이미지이기 때문에 약간 일반적인 문제는 모든 이미지에 적용 할 수 없습니다
very high dimensional objects with lots of pixels and so these jerseys will be
픽셀의 제비 등이 유니폼이 될 것입니다 매우 높은 차원 객체
huge and people try to do things like only doing whitening locally so you
거대하고 사람들은 당신 때문에 로컬 미백하고 같은 일을하려고
would see slide lightning filter through your image especially and that used to
특히 이미지를 통해 슬라이드 번개 필터를 확인하고 그 사용 것
be down several years ago but it's not as common now it doesn't seem to matter
몇 년 전 다운하지만 중요하지 않는 것 지금과 같은 일반적인 아니다
too much ok to wait initialization
초기화를 기다릴 너무 많이 확인
very very important topic one of the reasons that I think early neural
아주 아주 중요한 주제 일찍 신경을 생각하는 이유 중 하나
networks didn't quite work with as well as because people are not careful enough
네트워크는 상당히으로뿐만 아니라 사람들이 충분히주의하지 않기 때문에 같은 작동하지 않았다
with this so one of the first things I will look at is first of all how not to
내가 볼 것이다 첫 번째 일이 그렇게 한 모든 첫 번째로 어떻게하지에
do it in this legislation so in particular you might be tempted to just
당신은 단지에 유혹 될 수 있습니다 특히 있도록이 법안에 할
say ok let's start off at the weights are equal to zero and you that in your
당신을 것을 제로에 동일한 가중치에서 시작하자하고 확인을 말하여
network says it was like a 10 layer neural network and you said always 20
네트워크는 10 층 신경망처럼이었고, 당신은 항상 20 말했다 말한다
why doesn't that work why isn't that a good idea as well go ahead
왜 그 일이 왜 좋은 생각은 잘 진행되지 않는 것을
basically just all your neurons at the same thing in backdrop they will behave
기본적으로 배경에서 같은 일에 그냥 모든 신경 세포는 동작합니다
the same way and so there's nothing as we call it what you call it
당신이 그것을 부르는 우리가 전화와 동일한 방법과 그렇게 아무것도 없다
symmetry breaking so all the other computing saying stuff and so they will
대칭 그래서 다른 모든 컴퓨팅 말하는 물건을 깨는 그래서 그들은 것
all look the same they'll compete the same gradients and so on so not the best
모두 동일한 구배를 경쟁 할 것 같은 등 그렇게하지 ​​가장 깨끗하게
thing is that people use small numbers small random numbers so one way you can
것은 사람들이 당신이 할 수있는 한 가지 방법 있도록 작은 숫자를 작은 임의의 숫자를 사용하는 것입니다
do that for example that is a relatively common thing to do is you sample from
할 수있는 비교적 흔한 일이 예를 들어 그렇게하는 것은에서 당신 샘플입니다
you negotiate with 2010 one standard deviation so small random numbers so
당신은 2010 하나의 표준 편차가 너무 작은 임의의 숫자 때문에 협상
that's where W matrix Hollywood initialize it now
W 행렬은 할리우드 지금 초기화 곳이다
issue with this initialization is that it works ok but you'll find that it only
이 초기화에 문제가 확인 작동하지만 당신이 찾는 그것은 해당
works ok if you have small networks but as you start to go deeper and deeper
당신이 점점 더 깊이 갈 시작으로 당신이 작은 네트워크를 가지고 있지만 경우 확인 작업
would have to be much more careful about the nationalization and I'd like to go
국유화에 대해 훨씬 더 조심해야 할 것입니다 내가 가고 싶습니다
into exactly what breaks and how it breaks and bite breaks when you try to
정확하게는 휴식과 나누기 어떻게 당신이하려고 할 때 휴식을 물린로
do these naive initialisation strategies and try to have deep networks so let's
이 순진 초기화 전략을 수행하고 깊은 네트워크를 가지고 그렇게하자하려고
look at what goes wrong so what I've written here is a small book so what
잘못되면 어떻게 보면 그래서 내가 여기에 쓴 것은 작은 책이다 그래서 뭐
we're doing here is going to step through this just briefly I'm sampling a
우리는 내가 샘플링하고있어이 그냥 간단히 단계별로 가고 여기 일을하는지
dataset of 1,000 points that are 500 dimensional and then I'm creating a
차원 (500)이며, 그 다음 내가 만드는거야 1,000 점의 집합
whole bunch of hidden layers and nonlinearities so say right now we have
숨겨진 레이어 및 비선형의 전체 무리 그래서 우리가 지금 당장 말
10 layers of 500 units and we're using 10 h and then I'm doing here as I'm just
(10) 500 단위의 층 우리는 10 시간을 사용하고 난 그냥 해요으로 나는 여기서 뭐 해요
basically taking unit gosh and data and I'm forwarding it through the network
기본적으로 단위 세상에 및 데이터를 복용하고 난 네트워크를 통해 전달 해요
and with this particular initialization strategy where right now that
어디 바로 지금이 특정 초기화 전략
initialization strategy is what I described in previous slide see sample
초기화 전략은 내가 이전 슬라이드 참조 샘플에 설명 된 것입니다
from gushing he's killed by serb 101 so what I'm doing here in this part because
분출에서 그는 내가이 부분 때문에 여기에서하고 있어요 그래서 세르비아 (101)에 의해 살해있어
I'm bored propagating this network which is right now made up of just a series of
지금은 그냥 시리즈로 구​​성되어이 네트워크를 전파 지루 해요
layers of the same size so if ten layers of $500 and I'm for propagating with
같은 크기의 레이어 $ 500 그렇다면 열 층과 나는 함께 전파를위한 해요
this initialization strategy for a unit gushing data and what what I want to
단위 분출 데이터와 I가 원하는 것에 대해이 초기화 전략
look at is what happens to the statistics of the hidden neurons
숨겨진 뉴런의 통계에 일어나는 것이다 봐
activations throughout the network with this initialization so we're going to
이 초기화와 네트워크를 통해 활성화 그래서 우리는 거 야
look specifically at the mean and standard deviation and we're going to
평균과 표준 편차에 구체적으로 보면 우리가가는거야
plot the mean standard deviation and we're going to block the histograms so
평균 표준 편차를 플롯 우리는 그렇게 히스토그램을 차단하는거야
we take all this data through and then say at the fifth player we're going to
우리는을 통해 모든 데이터를 가지고 우리가 가고있는 다섯 번째 플레이어에서 말
look at what the what values did take on inside the fifth or sixth or seventh
뭐라고 값이 다섯이나 여섯 또는 일곱 번째 내부에 가지고 무슨 짓을했는지 봐
where we're going to make histograms of those so with this initialization if you
우리는 당신이 만약이 초기화와 함께, 그래서 사람들의 히스토그램을 만들어가는 곳
run this experiment you end up it ends up looking as follows
그것은 다음과 같이보고 끝나는 당신은 결국이 실험을 실행
so here I am printing it out we start off with a mean of zero as their
그래서 여기에 내가 그것을 밖으로 인쇄하고 우리는 0의 평균으로 시작 그들의
division of one that's our data and now I'm for propagating
하나의 부문은 우리의 데이터의 그것과 지금은 전파를위한 해요
as I go to 10 player in the mean we're using 10 age so tender age of symmetry
나는 우리가 대칭의 10 세 정도로 부드러운 나이를 사용하고 평균 10 플레이어에 가서
so as you might expect the mean states around zero but the standard deviation
당신이 제로 주변의 평균 상태에 있지만, 표준 편차를 예상대로 그렇게
look at what happens to it started off at 110 division was 2.2 then pulling
그것을 어떻게되는지를 보면 110 부문 진형 2.2은 당기했다
2004 and its plummets down to zero for the standard deviation of these neurons
2004 년과 다음 뉴런의 표준 편차에 대한 구심 제로 다운
just goes down 20 looking at the histograms here at every single air at
그냥 하나 하나 공기에 여기 히스토그램을보고 아래로 20 간다
the first layer the histogram is reason
히스토그램 이유 제 층
so we have a spread of numbers between 11 and then what ends up happening to it
그래서 우리는 11 사이의 숫자의 확산을하고 무엇은 일어나고 끝
just collapses to a tight distribution at exactly zero so what ends up
다만 정확히 제로 그래서 무슨 일이 끝에서 꽉 분포 ​​축소
happening with this initialization produced only our network is all the 10
우리의 네트워크 생산이 초기에 발생하는 모든 10
H neurons just end up out the team just 20 so at the last layer these are tiny
H 뉴런은 20 그래서 마지막 계층에서 이러한 작은 수있는 팀에서 결국
numbers of like near zero and so all occupations basically become zero and
같은 제로에 가까운 그래서 모든 직업은 기본적으로 0이된다 및 번호
why is this an issue
왜이 문제입니다
think about what happens to the dynamics of the backward pass to the gradients
그라디언트에 후방 패스의 역학에 무슨 생각
when you have tiny numbers in the activations your texts are tiny numbers
당신이 정품 인증에 작은 번호가있을 때 당신의 텍스트는 작은 숫자입니다
on the last few layers
지난 몇 층에
what what do these ingredients look like on the way it's in these layers and what
어떤 이들 성분처럼 무엇을 중요시하는 방법에 이들 계층 무엇에 있어요
happens to the backward pass the first of all suppose my so there is a layer
후방에 발생하는 모든의 첫 번째 내 너무 층이 가정 통과
here that looks at some later before it and almost all the inputs are so tiny
여기에 나중에 전에 몇 가지를 살펴보고 거의 모든 입력은 너무 작은 것을
numbers that's the x axis a tiny number what is the gradient what do you expect
당신이 기대하는 일 기울기가 무엇인지 작은 수의 X 축입니다 번호
to the gradients for the W to be in that case for those layers you some very
그라디언트에 W 해당 레이어의 경우에하는 주셔서 매우
small so why would they be very small W will be equal to x times the gradient
작은 왜 그들은 것입니다 매우 작은 W는 X 시간 기울기와 동일합니다
from the top
상부로부터
ok and so effects are tiny numbers than your reasons for WR tiny numbers as well
확인 등의 효과뿐만 아니라 WR 작은 숫자에 대한 이유보다 작은 숫자입니다
and so these guys will basically have almost no reason to cannulated now we
그래서이 사람은 기본적으로 지금 유관 거의 이유가 없습니다 우리
can also look at what happens with these matrices again we we took data that was
또한 다시이 행렬에 무슨 볼 수 있습니다 우리는 우리이었다 데이터를했다
distributed as a unit caution and the beginning and then we ended up
단위주의와 처음으로 배포 한 후 우리는 결국
multiplying it by W and activation function and we saw that basically
W 및 활성화 기능에 의해 그것을 곱 우리는 기본적으로 그 보았다
everything goes to zero this just collapses over time and think about the
모든 이것은 단지 시간이 지남에 붕괴하고 생각 제로로 간다
backward pass as we change the gradient through these layers and
뒤로 패스 우리가 이러한 레이어를 통해 그라데이션을 변경 같이
back-propagation what we're doing effectively is some of the gradient kind
우리가 효과적으로 무슨 일을하는지 다시 전파는 그라데이션 종류의 일부입니다
of folks off into our gradient W and we saw the numbers but then threw back
우리 그라데이션 W에 사람들 오프의 우리는 숫자를 보았다하지만 다시 던졌다
propagation we're going through agreements effects and so we end up
전파는 우리가 계약 효과를 통해거야 그리고 우리는 결국
doing when we backdrop through here is what you get
여기를 통해 우리 배경은 당신이 무엇을 얻을 때 일
multiplying by W again and again at every single layer and if you take unit
당신이 장치를 가지고가는 경우 모든 단일 계층에서 또 다시 W에 의해 곱한
gushing data and you multiply by WC at this scale you can see that everything
이 규모에서 화장실에 의해 다중 데이터를 분출하면 당신은 모든 것을 볼 수 있습니다
goes to zero and the same thing will happen then backward pass were
제로하고 같은 일이 후 뒤로 패스했다 일어날 간다
successively multiplying by W as we back propagation two acts on every single air
연속적으로 매일 공기에 우리 다시 전파로 W에 의해 두 행위를 곱하여
and we are you that this gradient which started off with reasonable numbers from
우리는 당신을있는 것과 합리적인 숫자 진형이 그라데이션
your loss function will end up just going toward zero as you keep doing this
당신의 손실 함수는이 일을 계속 같이 그냥 0으로가는 종료됩니다
process and you end up with gradients here that are basically just tiny tiny
프로세스 및 당신은 기본적으로 작은 단지 작은 여기에 그라디언트 결국
numbers and so you basically end up with very very low gradients throughout this
숫자는 그래서 당신은 기본적으로이 전반에 걸쳐 매우 매우 낮은 기울기와 끝까지
network because of this reason and this is something that we refer to as banish
이 때문에 이유의 네트워크 및 이것은 우리가 추방으로 참조 뭔가
ingredient as this gradient travels through with this particular
이 그라데이션 등의 성분이 특정과를 통해 이동
initialization you can see that the group the magnitude of the green we'll
초기화는 녹색의 그​​룹이 크기를 볼 수 있습니다 우리는거야
just go down when we used this in one of two so we can try different extreme
단지 우리가 두 가지 중 하나를 사용 사용될 때 가서 우리는 극단적 인 다른 시도 할 수 있습니다
instead of the scaling here as we scale with bunny negative to you can try
당신이 시도 할 수 있습니다에 여기 스케일링 우리는 토끼와 음의 확장으로 대신
different scale of the W matrix at initialization so suppose I try 110001
초기화에서 W 매트릭스의 다른 규모 그래서 나는 110001 시도 가정
will see another funny thing happened because now we overshot the other way in
이제 우리는 다른 방법을 오버 슈트 때문에 또 다른 재미 일이 일어 볼 수 있습니다
a sense that you can see that well maybe it's best to look at the decisions here
당신이 잘 볼 수있는 감각은 아마 여기에서 결정을보고하는 것이 가장 좋습니다
you can see that everything is completely saturated these 10 hrs either
당신은 모든 것이 완전히 중이 10 시간을 포화 볼 수 있습니다
all negative one or all one i mean the distribution is really just everything
모든 부정적인 하나 내가 분포를 의미하는 모든 사람은 정말 모든 것
is super-saturated your entire network of neurons throughout the network card
네트워크 카드를 통해 신경 세포의 전체 네트워크를 슈퍼 포화
either negative 101 because the weights are too large and they keep adding that
하나 음 (101) 무게가 너무 큰 그들은 것을 계속 추가하기 때문에
anyone else because this course that end up going through the non-linearity are
비선형 성을 겪고 결국이 과정이기 때문에 다른 사람
just very large because the weights are large and so everything is super
단지 매우 큰 가중치가 큰 그래서 모든 슈퍼 때문에
saturated so what are the ingredients flowing through your network is just
네트워크가 그냥 통해 재료가 흐르는 무엇 때문에 포화
terrible it's complete disaster right that's just zeros for every just
끔찍한 그냥 모든 단지에 대한 제로로의 완벽한 재난 권리입니다
exponentially 0 and you die so you can train for a very long time and where
기하 급수적으로 0 당신은 그래서 당신은 매우 긴 시간과 훈련을 할 수 죽을
you'll see when this happens is your losses just nothing at all because
이 모든 때문에 당신의 손실 그냥 아무것도되는 일이 없을 때 당신은 볼 수 있습니다
nothing is back propagating because all the neurons are saturated and nothing is
모든 신경 세포가 포화 아무것도하지 않기 때문에 아무것도 다시 전파되지 않습니다
being updated so this initialization as you might expect actually is like super
당신이 실제로 예상대로이 초기화가 슈퍼처럼 있도록 업데이트되는
tricky to set and it needs to be kind of in this particular case it needs to be
까다로운 설정하고 그것이 있어야 특히이 경우 가지 있어야
somewhere between 10 10 10 K and so
어딘가 10 10 10 K 등 사이
so you can be slightly more principled instead of trying some different values
그래서 당신은 약간 더 대신 몇 가지 다른 값을 시도의 원칙에 따른 될 수있다
and there are some papers written on this so for example in 2010 there was a
2010 년 예를 들어이 있었다 있도록이 작성 몇 가지 서류가
proposal for what we now call the initialisation from go out at all and
우리가 지금의 초기화를 호출하는 것에 대해 제안이 전혀 나가서
the kind of went through and they looked at the expression for the variance of
의 종류가 겪은 그들은의 분산에 대한 표현 보았다
your neurons and you can read this out and you can basically propose a specific
당신의 신경 및이를 읽을 수 있습니다 당신은 기본적으로 특정을 제안 할 수있다
initialization strategy for how you spell your gradients so I don't have to
그래서 난 필요 없어 당신이 당신의 구배를 주문 방법에 대한 초기화 전략
try 2001 I don't have to try one or whatever else they recommend this kind
나는 그들이 이런 종류의 추천 어떤 다른 하나를 시도 할 필요가 없습니다 2001 시도
of initialization we divided by the square root of the number of inputs for
초기화 우리는 입력의 수의 제곱근으로 나눈
every single neuron
하나 하나 신경
lots of inputs then you end up with lower weights and intuitively that makes
입력의 많은 당신은 낮은 무게와 끝까지 직관적으로 그 수
sense because you're doing more with you have more stuff that goes into your
당신이 더 많은 일을하고 있기 때문에 의미 당신은 당신으로가는 더 많은 물건을 가지고와
weight it some so you want less of an interaction to all of them and if
무게 일부는 그래서 당신은 그들 모두와 경우 상호 작용이 덜합니다
smaller number of units that are feeding into your lair when you want larger
더 큰하려는 은신처로 공급되는 단위의 적은 수의
weights because then there's only a few of them and you want to have a variance
무게 다음 거기에 그들 중 몇 그리고 당신은 변화를 원하기 때문에
of 18 just back up a bit
18의 조금 백업
the idea here is they were looking at the single neuron no activation
여기에 아이디어는 그들은 하나의 신경 세포 더 활성화에서 찾고있다
functions include is just the linear neuron and all they're saying is if you
함수는 선형 신경 세포입니다 포함하고있는 경우가 말을하는지 모든입니다
want if you're getting your data as input and you like this learner on to
당신이 입력으로 데이터를 받고하는 경우 원하는 당신에게이 학습자를 좋아한다
have a variance of one then you should initialize your weights with this amount
다음은이 금액하여 가중치를 초기화해야 하나의 분산을
and in the notes I going to exactly how this is derived is just us two standard
그리고 노트에 난이 파생하는 방법을 정확하게 단지 우리 두 개의 표준되어가는
deviations and basically this is a reasonable initialization so I can use
편차 내가 사용할 수 있도록 기본적으로이 합리적인 초기화입니다
that instead and you can see that if I use it here
대신 당신은 볼 수 여기를 사용하는 경우
the distributions end up being more sensible over again looking at the
분포 다시보고를 통해보다 합리적인 끝나게
history between negative one on one of these ten agents and you get a more
이러한 열 에이전트 중 하나에 부정적 일 간의 역사와 당신은 더 많은 것을 얻을 수
sensible number here and you actually have your within the active region of
현명한 여기 수와 실제로의 활성 영역 내에서이
all these teenagers and so you can expect that this will be a much better
모든 청소년은 그래서 당신이 훨씬 더 좋을 것으로 예상 할 수있다
initialization because things are in the active regions and things will train
초기화 가지 활성 영역에있는 것들 훈련 때문에
from the start nothing is super saturated in the beginning the reason
시작 무에서 시작하는 이유 슈퍼 포화
that this doesn't just end up being very nice and the reason we still have
이 단지 아주 좋은, 우리가 아직도 가지고있는 이유 끝나게하지 않습니다
convergence down here is because this paper doesn't take into account the
이 문서는 계정을 고려하지 않기 때문에 아래로 여기 융​​합이다
nonlinearities in this case the tenant and so the tennis nonlinearity and up
이 경우 비선형 세입자 등 테니스 비선형 최대
like kind of the forming your statistics of the variance throughout and so if you
전체에 분산의 형성 통계의 종류 같은 그래서 당신 경우
start this off it and and up still doing something to distribution in this case
그것을 떨어져이 시작하고 최대 여전히이 경우 유통에 일을
it seems that the standard deviation goes down but it's not as dramatic as if
이 표준 편차가 다운 될 것 같다하지만 경우처럼 극적인 아니다
you were to set this bye bye just trial
이 안녕 안녕을 설정 단지 시험했다
there and so this is like a reasonable initialisation
그래서 이것은 합리적인 초기화처럼 거기입니다
to use internal networks compared to just setting at the 2001 and so people
비교하여 내부 네트워크를 사용하는 단지 2001 그래서 사람들을 설정합니다
end up using the same practice sometimes but so this works in the case of 10 age
때로는 같은 관행을 사용하게하지만, 그래서 이것은 10 세의 경우 작동
does something reasonable it turns out if you try to put it into a rectified
당신이 정류에 넣어하려고하면 합리적인 무언가를 그것은 밝혀
linear unit network it doesn't work as well and decreasing divisions will be
선형 단위 네트워크는 그것뿐만 아니라 작동하지 않고 감소 부문이 될 것입니다
much more rapid so looking at a rally in Tehran and the first layer it has some
훨씬 더 빠른 그래서 테헤란에서 집회를보고 첫 번째 레이어는 몇 가지가 있습니다
distribution and then distribution as you can see just gets more and more
당신이 볼 수있는 분배하고 분배는 더욱 더 얻는다
picky at zero so more and more neurons are activated with this initialization
제로 그래서 점점 더 많은 뉴런에서 까다로운이 초기화로 활성화된다
so using the initialisation in a rectify layer layer net does not do good things
그래서 바로 잡기 층 층 그물에 초기화를 사용하는 것은 좋은 일을하지 않습니다
and so again thinking about this paper they don't actually talk about
그래서 다시 그들이 실제로에 대해 얘기하지 않는이 논문에 대해 생각
nonlinearities and the relevant Iran's the computer this weighted sum which is
비선형 및 관련이란의 컴퓨터입니다이 가중 합
within their demand here but not after the way that something you do so you
방법 후 여기에 있지만 그들의 수요에서 뭔가 당신은 그래서 당신이 수행하는 것이
kill half of the distribution you set it to 0 and intuitively what that does to
당신이 직관적으로 그가 무엇을 0으로 설정하고 분배의 절반을 죽일
your distribution of your up but basically half their variants and so it
당신의 최대의 배포하지만, 기본적으로 절반 변형 등이
turns out it was proposed in this paper just last year in fact someone said
이 사실은 누군가에 작년에 본 논문에서 제안되었다 밝혀 말했다
basically look there's a factor of two you're not a company for because he's
기본적으로 당신은 그가 때문에에 대한 회사 아니에요 2 배 거기에 보면
really you don't know ron's they effectively happy or variants each time
정말 당신은 론의 효과적으로 행복을 모르거나 때마다 변형하지 않는다
because you take everything so you have not gotten inputs you take them through
당신이 입력을 확보하지 못했 있도록 모든 것을 가지고 있기 때문에 당신이 그들을 통해 소요
your nonlinearity you have you gotten stuff I would but not you really do that
당신의 비선형 당신은 당신이 나는 것 물건을 받고 있지만 당신이 정말로 그렇게하지
and so you end up having two variants seem to account for it with it too and
그래서 당신이 두 가지 변종을 가진 끝 그것도으로 고려하는 것 그리고
when you do that then you get proper distribution specifically for Darrell in
당신은 당신이 데럴을 위해 특별히 적절한 분포를 얻을 수행 할 때
Iran and so in this initialization were you using nets you have to worry about
이란 등이 초기화에 사용 된 그물하면 약을 걱정할 필요가
that extra tax revenue and everything will come up nicely and you won't get
여분의 세수 모든 것이 잘 올 것이다 당신은받지 않습니다
this factor of two that keeps building up and it screws up your activations
이 구축 계속 두 가지의 요인과는 나사까지 당신의 활성화를
exponentially so basically this is tricky tricky stuff and it really
기하 급수적 그래서 기본적으로이 까다로운 까다로운 물건과는 정말
matters in practice in practice in their paper for example to compare having the
예를 들어 자신의 논문에서 연습에 연습 문제는을 가진 비교
factor if you are not having a factor too and it matters we have really deep
당신이 너무 요인을 가지고 있지 않으며이 중요한 경우 요인 우리가 정말 깊이가
networks in this case I think they had a few dozen players if you account for the
당신이 고려하는 경우이 경우 네트워크는 나는 그들이 수십 플레이어를 가졌다 고 생각
fact that you converge if you don't count reduction to you does nothing just
당신은 아무것도 그냥하지 않습니다에 당신이 감소를 계산하지 않는 경우가 수렴한다는 사실
zero lots ok
제로 많이 확인
so very important stuff you really need to think it through you to be careful
그래서 당신이 정말 필요한 매우 중요한 물건을 조심해야 당신을 통해 그것을 생각하는
with inflation if it's incorrectly such bad things happen and so specifically
그것은 잘못 같은 나쁜 일이 너무 구체적으로 어떻게하고 있는지 인플레이션
the case if you have known that works with rail units there is a correct
이 레일 장치와 함께 작동 당신이 알고있는 경우 케이스는 정확
answer to use and that's this initialization from coming so this is
사용 대답하고 그래서 이것이 오는이 초기화이다
partly this is partly why your remark for a long time as we just i think
부분적으로이 오랫동안 당신의 말은 우리가 내가 생각하는 일부 이유
people didn't fully maybe appreciate just how difficult this was to get right
사람들은 완전히 어쩌면이 잘 얻을 수 있었다 얼마나 어려운 감사하지 않았다
and Turkey and so I just like to point out that proper initialization basically
터키 그래서 난 그냥 적절한 초기화 기본적으로 지적하고 싶은
active area of research you can see the papers are still being published on this
연구의 활성 영역은 당신이 논문은 아직이에 게시되고있다 볼 수 있습니다
a large number of papers just opposing different ways of initializing your
논문 다수 단지 초기화하는 다른 방법을 마주하여
networks these last few are interesting as well because they don't give you a
그들은 당신에게를 제공하지 않기 때문에 네트워크는 지난 몇도 흥미 롭다
formula for initializing they have these data driven waste of initializing
초기화 공식 그들은 이러한 데이터를 초기화 구동 폐기물이
networks and to take a batch of data you forward it to your network which is now
네트워크와 지금 당신은 당신의 네트워크에 전달할 데이터의 배치를 취할
an arbitrary network and you look at the variances that every single point in
임의의 네트워크와는 차이를 보면 그 모든 단일 지점에서
your network and intuitively you don't want your variances to go to zero you
네트워크 및 직관적으로 당신은 당신의 차이는 0으로 가고 싶지 않아
don't want them to explode you want everything to have roughly say like be a
원하지 않는 그들은 모든 약이 같은 일 말하고 싶은 폭발
unit caution throughout your network and so they entered a plea scale these
네트워크 전반에 걸쳐 단위주의는 그래서 그들은 항변 스케일이 입력
weights in your network so that you have roughly in the activation everywhere on
당신이 사방에 활성화에 크게 가질 수 있도록 네트워크에 무게
the order of that basically and so there are some data-driven techniques and line
그 순서는 기본적 등 일부 데이터 중심의 기술과 라인이 있습니다
of work on how to properly initialized ok so I'm going to go into some I'm
제대로 난 난 일부에 갈거야, 그래서 확인을 초기화하는 방법에 대한 작업
going to go into technique that alleviate a lot of these problems but
이러한 많은 문제를 완화하는 기술로 갈하지만
right now I could take some questions and they're only by dividing by the
지금 나는 몇 가지 질문을 수 그리고 그들은으로 나누어에만있어
variance possibly but then you're not being back propagation because if you
분산 가능하지만 다시없는거야 전파 당신이 경우 때문에
met with the gradient then it's not clear what your objective is anymore and
그라데이션 만난 후 당신의 목표는 더 이상 무엇인지 분명하지 않다과
so you're not getting necessarily gradient so this may be the only concern
그래서 당신은 그라데이션 반드시 못하고있어 그래서 이것은 유일한 문제가 될 수있다
I'm not sure what would happen if you can try to normalize the gradient I
난 당신이 그라데이션 I 정상화를 시도 할 경우 무슨 일이 일어날 지 확실하지 않다
think the method I'm going to propose in a bit
이 방법은 내가 조금에 제안 할 것 같네요
is actually doing something to the effect of that but in a clean way what's
실제로 그 효과에하지만 무엇 깨끗한 방법으로 일을하고있다
going to something that actually fix a lot of these problems in practice it's
실제로 그건 실제로 이러한 많은 문제를 해결 뭔가로 이동
called back to my vision and it was only proposed last year and so i cant even
나의 비전이라고하며 그것은 단지 작년에 제안하고, 그래서 심지어 캔트
covered this last year in this class but now I can actually helps a lot
이 클래스에서이 작년에 덮여 있지만, 지금은 실제로 많은 도움이 있습니다
ok and the basic idea maximization paper is ok you want roughly unit gotten
확인하고 기본 개념을 극대화 종이는 대략 기기가 받고 싶은 괜찮습니다
activations in every single part of your network and so just just do that just
네트워크의 모든 단일 부분에서 활성화하고 그래서 그냥 그냥 그냥 할
just make them you know caution ok you can do that because making something
그냥 만들 당신은 당신이 할 수있는 확인주의를 알고있는 무언가를 만들기 때문에
unit caution is a completely different function and so it's ok you can
단위주의는 완전히 다른 기능이며, 그래서 확인 당신이 할 수 있어요
propagate through it and see what they do is you taking me back from your data
그것을 통해 전파하고 데이터에서 날 다시 복용 무엇 그들이 참조
and you're picking through your network we're going to meet
당신은 우리가 만날거야 네트워크를 통해 따기있어
inserting these specialization layers into your network and the best
네트워크와 최상의으로 이러한 전문화 층을 삽입
normalization layers they take your input X and they make sure that every
정규화 층은 귀하의 입력 X를 가지고 그들은 모든 있는지 확인
single feature dimension across the batch you have unit gushing activations
배치에서 하나의 기능 치수는 단위 분출 활성화를
so he had a batch of hundred examples going through the network maybe this is
그래서 그는 어쩌면이있는 네트워크를 통과 백 예제의 배치를했습니다
a good example here is even better activation so many things in your money
여기에 좋은 예는 당신의 돈에 더 나은 활성화 너무 많은 일을하다
back and have D features or deactivation of neurons that are at some point some
뒤로 어떤 점에있다 D 기능 또는 신경 세포의 불 활성화가 일부
part and this is an input your back later
부분이는 다시 나중에 입력
so this is a major subjects of activations and nationalization
그래서 이것은 활성화 및 국유화의 주요 주제이다
effectively evaluate the empirical mean and variance along every single feature
효과적으로 모든 단일 기능을 함께 경험 평균과 분산을 평가
and it just divided by it so whatever your ex was just make sure that every
그것은 단지 어떤 있도록 전 그냥 확인했다 그것으로 나눈 모든 것을
single column here has unit is a Univision and so that's a perfectly
단일 열 여기서 단위는 Univision의입니다 가지고 있으며, 그래서 완벽하게있어
differentiable function and just applies it at every single feature or activation
미분 기능은 모든 단일 기능 또는 활성화에 그것을 적용
independently across the batch so you can do that turns out to be a very good
독립적으로 배치를 통해 당신은 아주 좋은 것으로 판명 할 수 있도록
idea now one problem with this team so this is the way this will work as well
아이디어는 지금이 팀과 함께 하나의 문제는 그래서 이것은이뿐만 아니라 작동 방법입니다
have normally we have followed by nonlinearity
일반적으로 우리는 비선형 다음에 한 한
party network of this now we're going to be inserting these nationalization
이 파티 네트워크 이제 우리는 이러한 국유화를 삽입 할거야
layers right after political heirs or equivalently after convolutional layers
바로 정치 상속인 후 또는 동등 길쌈 층 후에 층
as well CCNA with commercial networks and basically we can start them there
상용 네트워크와 잘 CCNA 등 기본적으로 우리가 그들을 시작할 수 있습니다
and they make sure that everything is gushing at every single step of the
그들은 모든이의 매 단계에서 분출되어 있는지 확인
network because we just make it so
우리가 그냥 그렇게 만들 있기 때문에 네트워크
and one problem I think up with this this is that it seems like a unnecessary
내가이이 함께 생각하는 한 가지 문제는 그것이 불필요한 것 같아 것입니다
constraint so when you put it back here after that the outputs will definitely
제약 그래서 당신은 후에 여기 다시 넣을 때 출력은 확실히 것
be gushing because you normalize them but it's not clear that 10 H actually
당신이 그들을 정상화 때문에 분출 될 수 있지만 명확하지 않다가 10 H 실제로
once to recede unit caution inputs so if you think about the the form of 10 H it
당신이 10 H의 형태에 대해 생각, 그래서 만약 한 번 단위주의 입력을 후퇴에
has a specific skill to it it's not clear that they're all that work once to
그들이에 한 번 작동 모든 것을 걸 분명하지 않다 그것에 특정 기술을 가지고
have this hard constraint of making sure that outputs are exactly you negotiate
출력은 당신이 협상 정확히 것을 확인이 어려운 제약 조건이
before the 10 TH because you like the network to pick if it wants your 10 each
10 TH 전에 당신은 당신의 10 각을 원하는 경우 선택하는 네트워크를 좋아하기 때문에
other what's to be more or less diffuse more or less saturated and right now it
지금 그것을 더 많거나 적은 포화 확산 및 더 많은 이하로 무엇이 다른
will be able to death so a small patch on top of it this is the second part of
그것은이 상단에 작은 패치의 두 번째 부분, 그래서 죽음을 수있을 것입니다
haitian is not going to normalize acts but after normalization you live network
아이 티어 행위를 정상화하지 않을하지만 정상화 한 후에는 네트워크를 살
to shift by gamma and had to be for every single feature and so this allows
감마으로 이동하고 모든 단일 기능에 대한 있어야했다 그래서이 허용하는
the network to do and these are our parameters so gamma and be here are
네트워크가 수행하는 이들은 감마 그래서 우리의 매개 변수이며 수있어
parameters that we're going to back to back up into and they just allow the
우리가 다시거야 매개 변수로 백업하고 그들은 단지 허용
network 22 shipped after your normal ICU negotiate they allow this bomb to shift
일반 ICU 후 배송 네트워크 (22)는이 폭탄이 이동 할 수 있도록 협상
and scale if the network wants to and so we initialize the presumably webb 110 or
규모가 네트워크가 원하는 경우 우리가 초기화 아마도 웹의 110
something like that and then we can the network can choose to adjust them and by
뭐 그런 다음 우리는 네트워크를 조정하도록 선택할 수 수에 의해
adjusting these you can imagine that once we feed into 10 H
당신은 우리가 10 H로 공급하면 상상이 수 조정
the network can choose through the backdrop signal to make it any more or
네트워크가 더 이상 그것을 만들기 위해 배경 신호를 선택하거나
less picky or saturated in whatever way it once but you're not going to get into
덜 까다 롭고 또는 한 번 어떤 방식으로 포화하지만 당신은 들어갈 않을거야
this trouble where things just completely died or explode in the
일이 그냥 완전히 사망하거나 폭발이 문제
beginning of optimization and so things will train right away and then back
최적화의 시작 등 상황이 그때 바로 훈련한다
propagation can take over and can find you into overtime and not one more
전파는 이상이 걸릴 수 있습니다 하나 더 초과 근무로 당신을 찾을 수 없습니다
important feature is that if you set these gunmen be if you train them if my
중요한 기능을 사용하면이 무장 괴한을 설정하면 경우에 당신이 그들을 훈련하는 경우 것이 내
back propagation it happens that the end up taking the empirical variance and the
다시 전파는 말까지의 경험 분산 및 복용하는 것이 일
mean when you can see that basically the network has the capacity to undo the
당신이 기본적으로 네트워크가를 취소 할 수있는 능력을 가지고 볼 수있을 때 의미
nationalization so this part can learn to undo that part and so that's why back
이 부분은 그 부분을 취소 배울 수 국유화 있도록 그래서 왜 돌아 왔어
to realization and can act as an identity function or can learn to be an
및 실현에 식별 기능의 역할을 할 수 있습니다 또는 일을 배울 수
identity whereas before it couldn't and so when you have these best-known
정체성이 없었던 전 그래서 당신이있을 때이 가장 잘 알려진 반면,
players in their the network and threw back propagation learn to take it out or
자신의 네트워크에있는 플레이어와 전파를 다시 던졌다 그것을 꺼내 배우거나
it can learn to take advantage of it if it finds it helpful
그것은 유용한 찾으면 그것을 활용 배울 수
through the backdrop this will kind of workout so that's just a nice point to
배경으로 통해 운동이 의지의 종류는 그에게 단지 좋은 점, 그래서
have and so basically there are several properties so this is the right number
이 오른쪽 숫자가 수 있도록이 때문에 기본적으로 몇 가지 속성이있다
them as I described my properties are that it improves the gradient flow
이들 제 특성은 구배 흐름을 개선한다는 것이다 I은 설명 된 것과
through the network allows for higher learning rates so your network and learn
네트워크는 고등 교육 비율 때문에 네트워크 배울 수 있습니다 통해
faster it reduces this is an important one introduces the strong dependence on
빨리이 중요한 하나는 강한 의존성에 대한 소개입니다 감소
initialization as you sweep through different choices of your initialisation
당신이 당신의 초기화의 다른 선택을 통해 청소로 초기화
scale you'll see that with and without bashing on you'll see a huge difference
당신이 당신을 학대하지 않고 그 표시됩니다 확장하는 것은 큰 차이를 볼 수 있습니다
with maximum you'll see a much more things will work for much larger
최대 당신은 훨씬 더 많은 것들이 훨씬 더 큰 위해 작동 볼 수 있습니다
settings of the initial scale and so you don't have to worry about it as much it
초기 규모의 설정 및 그래서 당신이없는만큼 걱정에
really helps out with this put point and one more subtle thing to point out here
정말이 넣어 포인트와 아웃하는 데 도움이 하나 더 미묘한 점은 여기에서 지적
is it kind of access of money from a realization and it reduces the need for
그것을 실현에서 돈의 액세스의 종류와 그 필요성에 대한 감소
a drop of which will go into in a bit later in class but the way it acts as a
한 방울의 클래스에 나중에 비트에 들어갈되지만 방법은이 역할을
funny regularization is when you have some kind of an input X and go through
당신이 입력 X의 어떤 종류를 가지고 통과 할 때 재미 정규화입니다
the network then its representation at some later in the network is basically
네트워크 다음 일부 나중에 네트워크에서의 표현은 기본적으로
not only function of it but it's also a function of whatever other examples
그것뿐만 아니라 기능뿐만 아니라 어떤 다른 예제의 함수의
happened to being a batch so
일괄 그렇게되기 위해서는 일
because whatever other examples are with you in that batch process completely
무엇 때문에 다른 예는 완전히 그 배치 과정에서 당신과 함께 있습니다
independently apparel fashion actually ties them together and so your
독립적으로 의류 패션은 실제로 함께하고 있으므로 그들을 묶어
representation that say like the thick layer of network is actually a function
네트워크의 두꺼운 층 같은 말 표현은 실제로 기능입니다
of whatever it back you happen to be sampled in and what does a generous your
무엇이든의 그것은 다시는 샘플링 할 일이하고 관대 한을 무엇을 당신의
place in the representation space on that later and this actually has a nice
나중에에 표현 공간에 배치하고이 실제로 좋은가
regularizing effect and so does generate sarcastically who this fact that you
효과를 정례화 등 빈정 생성 않는 사람 당신이이 사실을
happen to be in has this effect and so i don't realize it actually seems to
에 될 일이 것은이 효과를 가지고 있으며, 그래서 난 실제로 것 같다 모르고
actually help out of it
실제로 그것의 도움
ok and the test I'm passionate later by the way functions a bit differently you
확인 시험 나는 방법 기능 나중에 조금 다르게 당신을 열정적 해요
don't have a test time you want this to be a deterministic function so just a
이 결정은 함수로 원하는 테스트 시간 불과하므로없는
quick point that s time when you're using a Bachelor function differently in
다르게 학사 기능을 사용할 때 시간을 s의 빠른 점
particular you have this new and a sigma that you keep normalizing by so a test
특히 당신은 당신이 그렇게 시험에 의해 정규화를 유지하는이 새로운 시그마가
I'm just remember your view and Sigma across the dataset you can either
난 그냥 당신도 할 수있는 데이터 세트에서보기와 시그마을 기억 해요
computed like what is the mean and sigmoid every single point in the
평균 무엇처럼 계산하고 모든 단일 지점에서 S 상
network you can compute that once over your entire training center or you can
네트워크는 전체 교육 센터를 통해 한 번 그 계산하거나 수
just have a running some amusing six months while you're training and then
그 다음에 훈련하고있는 동안 단지 몇 가지 재미있는 육개월을 실행 한
make sure to remember that in the best player because it just time you don't
최고의 선수에 있기 때문에 그냥 시간이 있는지 기억 할 수 있도록 당신은하지 않습니다
want to actually estimate the empirical mean and variance across your back you
실제로 허리에 걸쳐 경험 평균과 분산을 추정 할 당신
want to just use those directly so because that's good you're not coming
그냥 당신이 오지 않을거야 좋은 때문에 그래서 직접들을 사용하려면
forward at this time so there's just a small detail and so that's any questions
이 단지 작은 세부 사항이고 그래서 질문은 그래서이 시간에 전달
about the national motorway so this is a good thing
전국 고속도로에 대한 그래서 이것은 좋은 일이
use it and your employees that actually your assignment
그것과 직원 실제로 할당을 사용
thank you so the question is that a slowdown at all it does so there is a
문제는 둔화 전혀은 그래서를가 않습니다 그래서 감사합니다
runtime penalty but you have to pay for it unfortunately I don't know exactly
그것은 불행하게도 내가 정확히 모르는에 대한 런타임 처벌하지만 당신은 지불해야
how expensive is I heard someone say like 30 percent even and so I don't know
나는 사람이 30 %처럼 말을 듣고 얼마나 비싼 경우에도 그래서 나도 몰라
actually I haven't fully checked this but basically there is a penalty because
실제로 나는 완전히이 확인되지 않은 있지만 기본적으로 패널티 때문에이있다
you have to do this normally you it's very common to be after every
당신은 당신이 모든 이후로 매우 일반적입니다 일반적으로이 작업을 수행해야
competition later and we have 250 calm like larry is you end up having all this
나중에 경쟁과 우리는 래리 같은 250 진정 당신이이 모든 것을 가지고 결국있다가
stuff buildup of questions raised the price we pay I suppose so yes so when
질문의 물건을 축적은 우리가 지불하는 가격을 인상 정말 그래 그래서 때를 가정
can you tell you maybe need national I think I'll come back to that in a in a
당신은 아마 내가이에 다시 그에게 올 거라고 생각 국가해야 알 수 있습니다
few slides will see like how can you detect that your network is not healthy
몇 슬라이드 네트워크가 건강하지 있음을 감지 할 수있는 방법을 같이 볼 수 있습니다
and then maybe you want a transnational ok so the learning process I have 20
다음 어쩌면 당신은 내가 20이 학습 과정 있도록 다국적 확인을 할
minutes I think I can do this is like 700 so I think we're fine so we trust
분 나는 그래서 우리는 우리가 신뢰 괜찮아요 생각이 700처럼 할 수 있다고 생각
our data we've decided let's let's decide on some for these purposes of
우리가 결정했습니다 우리의 데이터는의는의는 이러한 목적을 위해 어떤 결정합시다
these experiments I'm going to work with C for 10 and I'm going to use a
이 실험은 내가 10 C 작동거야 그리고 나는를 사용하는거야
two-layer neural network with safety had a nuanced and I'd like to give an idea
안전 두 층 신경 네트워크는 미묘한 차이를 가지고 있었고, 나는 아이디어를 제공하고 싶습니다
about like how this looks like impact is when your training neural networks like
이 충격과 같은 방법 등에 대해 같은 때 훈련 신경 네트워크입니다
how do you play with it
당신은 플레이 어떻게
where someone how do you actually converted to Primaris what does this
어디 사람이 어떻게 실제로이 무엇 Primaris로 변환 할
process of playing with a date on getting things to work look like in
일을 얻기에 날짜와 재생의 과정에서 같이 일을하는
practice and so I decided to try out a small neural network
연습하고 그래서 작은 신경 네트워크를 사용하기로 결정
preprocess my data and so the first kinds of things that I would look at if
내 데이터와 나는 경우에 보일 것이다 사물의 상기 제 1 종류의 전처리
I want to make sure that my prediction is correct them think things are working
내 예측이 그들에게 일을 작업하는 생각 보정되어 있는지 확인하려면
first of all I'm going to be initializing here a two-year neural
내가 갈거야 모두의 첫 번째는 여기에 2 년 신경을 초기화한다
network so weights and biases initializing was just naive
네트워크 초기화 무게와 편견 그냥 순진했다 그래서
initialization here because this is just a very small network so I can afford to
여기에 초기화이 그래서가 감당할 수있는 그냥 아주 작은 네트워크 때문에
maybe do just a naive sample from exhaustion and then this is a function
어쩌면 고갈에서 단지 순진 샘플을 수행 한 다음이 함수는
that basically going to train a neural network and I'm not showing you the
기본적으로 신경 네트워크를 양성하는 것 그리고 난 당신에게 보여주는 아니에요
implementation obviously but just one thing missing is returned your lost
구현 분명하지만 한 것은 당신의 손실을 반환 누락
their returns your premiums on your model parameters and so that the first
모델 매개 변수에 대한 그래서 먼저 자신의 반환 보험료
time I tried for example is i disable the regularization that's passed in the
내가 예를 들어 시도 시간이 나는에 전달되는 정규화를 사용하지 않도록한다
end and I make sure that my loss comes out
종료하고 난 내 손실이 나오는 것을 확인
act right so I mention this and previous lines so say I have 10 classes and
바로 그렇게 행동 나는이 언급 이전 라인 그래서 나는 10 수업을 말하기
support n im using soft classifier so I know that I'm expecting a loss of
내가의 손실을 예상하고있어 것을 알 수 있도록 부드러운 분류를 사용하여 지원 n 개의 메신저
negative log of one over 10 because that's that's an expression for the loss
그 때문에 10 일의 음의 로그가 그 손실에 대한 식이다
and that turns out to be 2.3 and so I put this and I get a lot of 2.3 so I
그리고는 2.3로 밝혀 그래서 나는 이것을두고 나는 그래서 2.3를 많이 얻을
know that basically the neural network is currently giving me a diffuse
기본적으로 신경망은 나에게 확산을주고 있음을 알 수
distribution over the classes because it doesn't know anything we've just been so
그것은 아무것도 모르기 때문에 클래스를 통해 배포 우리는 너무 봤는데
that sucks out the next thing I might check is that for example I cranked up
그 밖으로 짜증 나는 확인 수있는 다음 일은 예를 들어 I가 마약이다
the regularization and of course expect my loss to go up right because now we
정규화 물론 내 손실이 올라갈 것으로 예상 지금 때문에 우리
have this additional term in the objective and so that checks out so
목적이 추가 기간이 있고 그래서 그렇게 체크 아웃
that's nice
그 좋네요
different the next thing I would usually try to do it's a very good sanity check
난 보통은 아주 좋은 상태 검사의 수행하려고 할 것입니다 다른 다음 일
when you're working on their networks is try to take a small piece of your data
당신이 그들의 네트워크에서 작업 할 때 데이터의 작은 조각을하려고한다
and try to make sure you can over it you're trying to do just that small
당신은 당신은 단지 그 작은을 위해 노력하고 그 위에 수 있는지 확인하려고
piece some twenty takes like say a sample of like 20 training examples and
스물 같이합니다 일부는 추천 훈련 예제의 샘플을 말 조각
28 labels and I just make sure that I trained on that small piece and I just
(28) 레이블과 난 그냥 그 작은 조각에 훈련 있는지 확인하고 그냥
make sure that I can get a loss of basically near zero I can fully over fit
내가 완전히 적합으로 초과 할 수있는 제로 근처에 기본적으로 손실을 얻을 수 있는지 확인
that because if i cant over fit a tiny piece of my idea then things are
내가 이상 캔트이라면 내 생각의 작은 조각을 맞게 때문에 일이 그
definitely broken and so here I am starting the training and I'm starting
나는 훈련을 시작하고 난 시작 해요 확실히 그래서 여기에 깨진
with some random number of parameters here I'm not going to go into full
여기에 일부 매개 변수 임의의 숫자와 나는 전체에 들어갈 않을거야
details there but basically I make sure that my costs can go down to zero and
이 세부하지만 기본적으로 내 비용이 제로에 가서 할 수 있는지 확인하고
that I'm getting accuracy 100% on this tiny piece of data and that gives me
나는 데이터의이 작은 조각에 정확도 100 %를 받고 있어요 그 날을 준다
confidence that probably backdrop is working probably the update is working
아마 배경은 아마 업데이트가 작동하고있다 신뢰
the learning rate is set to somehow reasonably and so I can put a small
학습 속도는 어떻게 든 합리적으로 설정되고 그래서 작은을 넣을 수 있습니다
dataset not happy at this point in time maybe I'm thinking about scaling up to a
어쩌면 나는까지 확장에 대해 생각하고이 시점에서 행복하지 않은 데이터 세트
larger than something
뭔가보다 큰
so you should be able to overpower it sometimes I can try like say like one or
그래서 당신은 하나 같이 말처럼 시도 할 수 때때로을 압도 할 수 있어야한다
two or three examples you can really practice down and you should be able to
두 개 또는 세 개의 예제 당신이 정말로 아래로 연습 할 수 있습니다 당신은 할 수 있어야
afford even with smaller networks and so that's a very good sanity check because
더 작은 네트워크를 감당할 그래서 매우 좋은 상태 검사 때문에입니다
you can afford to have small networks and just make sure if you can't help it
당신은 작은 네트워크가 여유와 당신이 그것을 도울 수 있는지 확인 할 수 있습니다
implementations probably incorrect something's very funky was wrong so you
아마 잘못된 일이 매우 펑키의 구현은 그렇게 잘못
should not be scaling up your full day I said before you can pass the Senate
당신이 상원을 통과하기 전에 당신의 하루를 확장해서는 안 나는 말했다
check so basically the way I try to approach this is taking a small piece of
의 작은 조각을 복용 나는이 접근을 시도 그래서 기본적으로 방법을 확인
data and now we're scaling it up over but it's an arms coming up to like the
데이터 이제 우리는 이상 그것을 확장하고 있지만 무기가 좋아하는 올라오고 있어요
bigger dataset I'm trying to find the learning rate that works and you have to
더 큰 데이터 세트는 I 작동 학습을 검색하기 위해 노력하고있어 당신은에 있습니다
really play with this right you can just eyeball delivering great to have to find
정말 그냥 안구 찾아야하는 큰 제공 할 수 있습니다이 권리 플레이
the scale roughly some trying first the small learning rate like many negative
규모는 대략 몇 가지 먼저 많은 부정적인 같은 소규모 학습 속도를 시도
six and I see that the loss as bait barely barely going down so this lost
여섯와 나는 미끼로 손실이 겨우 겨우 그래서이 손실 추락 볼
this learning rate of one negative six is probably too small right nothing is
하나의 부정적인 육이 학습 속도는 아마 너무 작은 권리 아무것도 없다이다
changing of course there could be many other things wrong because they lost
그들은 손실 때문에 당연히 변경하면 다른 많은 문제가있을 수 있습니다
because in for like a million reasons but we passed the small sanity check so
하지만 용처럼 만 이유에서 우리는 너무 작은 정신 검사를 통과하기 때문에
I'm thinking that this is probably losses too low and I need you to hit by
나는 이것이 아마 손실이 너무 낮다는 것을 생각하고 그리고 난 당신에 의해 칠 필요
the way this is a fine example hear of something funky going on that is fun to
이 방법은가는 펑키 무언가의 좋은 예 듣는가 재미있다
think about my loss just barely went down but actually my training accuracy
겨우 내려 갔다 내 손실에 대해 생각하지만 실제로 내 훈련 정확도
shot up to 20% from the default 10% how does that make any sense how can I beat
그게 내가 이길 수 있는지 이해가 않는 방법 기본 10 %에서 20 %까지 촬영
by lost just barely changed but my costs my accuracy so good
손실에 의해 겨우 변경하지만 내 비용 내 정밀도가 너무 좋아
well much much better than 10% of that even possible
물론 훨씬 더 그게 가능의 10 % 이상
still
아직도
ok maybe not quite so think about how accuracy is computed and how this custom
확인 아마 꽤 정확도를 계산하는 방법에 대해 생각하는 방법이 사용자 지정
computer right now what's happening is your training so these scores are tiny
컴퓨터가 지금 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는지이 점수가 작은 그래서 당신의 훈련입니다
shifting your losses still roughly diffuse end up in the same loss but now
대략 확산 여전히 손실을 이동 지금 같은 손실에서 생을 마감하지만,
you're correct answers are not tiny bit more probably and so we actually
당신은 정답이없는 작은 조금 더 아마 그래서 우리는 실제로있어
competing the accuracy D art maxi class is actually end up doing the correct one
실제로 정확성 D 기술의 맥시 클래스입니다 경쟁 올바른 일을 끝낼
of these are some of the fun things you run into when you actually trained some
이들의 당신은 당신이 실제로 어떤 훈련시에 실행 재미 것들 중 일부입니다
of the stuff you do have to think about the expressions ok so now I start I
물건의 확인을 그래서 지금 내가 시작 표현식에 대해 생각해야합니까
tried very low learning rate things are barely happening soon I'm going to go to
시도 매우 낮은 학습 속도 일들이 거의 내가에 갈거야 곧 일어나고
the other extreme and I'm going to try out the learning 32 million what could
내가 무엇을 할 수있을 학습 32,000,000을 시도거야 극단적 인 기타
possibly go wrong so what happens in that case you get some weird errors and
아마도 당신은 몇 가지 이상한 오류가 발생할 수 있으므로 어떤 경우에 발생하는 잘못과
things explode to get nancy really fun stuff happens so ok one of the 1,000,000
일이 낸시 정말 재미있는 물건은 1,000,000 중 하나 너무 좋아 어떻게 얻을 폭발
this probably too high as what I'm thinking at this point so then I tried
내가 노력 제가 그럼이 시점에서 생각하고 등이 아마 너무 높은
to narrow in on rough region that actually gives me a decrease in my cost
거친 지역에있는 좁힐 실제로 나에게 내 비용의 감소를 제공하는
thread that's what I'm trying to do with my binary search here and so at some
그게 내가 몇 가지 여기 나의 이진 검색으로 할 노력하고있어 무엇 스레드
point I get some idea about you know roughly where should I be cross
포인트 난 당신이 내가 십자가 있어야 할 곳에 대략 알고에 대한 몇 가지 아이디어를 얻을
validating
검증
like a proper optimization at this point I'm trying to find the best I promise
이 시점에서 적절한 최적화처럼 내가 약속 최선을 찾을려고
for my network right we like to do in practice is go from course to find
내 네트워크 권리를 우리가 찾는 과정에서 이동되는 연습 할 좋아
strategy so first I just have a rough idea by playing with it we're learning
전략은 그래서 처음 난 그냥 우리가 배우고 함께 연주하여 거친 생각을 가지고
Richard being then I do a course search are alarming rates of like a bigger a
리처드 난 코스 검색을 수행 한 후있는 것은 더 큰 유사한 속도를 놀라운된다
segment and then I repeat this process I look at what works and then I narrow in
세그먼트 후 내가 어떤 작품을보고 나서이 좁은이 과정을 반복
on the region's that work well ok do this here are quickly and your codes for
이 지역의 그 일을 잘 확인 여기에 이​​렇게 빨리 그리고 당신의 코드에 대한
example detect explosions and break out early it's like a nice step in terms of
예를 폭발을 감지하고 초기는 측면에서 좋은 단계처럼 탈옥
implementation so what I'm doing effectively here as I have a loop where
내가 루프 위치를 가지고 구현 그래서 효과적으로 여기서 뭘하는지
I sample my prime minister saying this case the regularization and learning
나는이 사건을 정규화 말을 배우는 내 총리 샘플
rate I sample them I train I get some results here so these are the accuracy
속도는 나는 이러한 정확성 그래서 내가 여기에 몇 가지 결과를 얻을 훈련을 샘플링
in the validation data and these are too high primaries that produced them and
검증 데이터에 이러한 그들을 생산 너무 높은 예비 선거는
some of the accuracy as you can see that they were quite well so 50% 40% some of
정확성의 일부는 당신은 그들이 몇 가지를 아주 잘 그래서 50 %였다 40 % 있음을 볼 수있다
them don't work well at all so this gives me an idea about what range of
그들 모두에서 잘 작동하지 않는 것은 그래서 이것은 나에게 어떤 범위에 대한 아이디어를 제공합니다
learning rates and regulations are working relatively well
학습의 요금 및 규정은 상대적으로 잘 작동됩니다
and when you do this optimization you can start out first with just a small
이 최적화를 수행 할 때 당신은 단지 작은 먼저 밖으로 시작할 수 있습니다
number of epochs you going to run for a very long time just run for a few
당신은 아주 긴 시간 동안 실행하려고 시대의 수는 몇 가지에 대해 실행
minutes you can already get the sense of what's working better than some other
다른보다 더 일하고 어떤 분은 이미 감각을 얻을 수 있습니다
things and also one note when you're optimizing over regularization learning
사물과 하나 노트 당신은 정규화 학습을 통해 최적화하고
rate it's best to simply walk space you don't just want to sample from a uniform
단순히 그냥 유니폼에서 샘플링하고 싶지 않은 공간을 산책하는 것이 가장 좋습니다 평가
distribution because these learning rates and regularization they act
유통이 학습 요금과 정규화 그들이 행동 때문에
multiplicative Lee on the dynamics of your back propagation and so that's why
곱셈 허리 전파의 역학에 리와는 그래서는 이유
you want to do this in lock space so you can see that I'm sampling from nigga 326
당신은 내가 흑인 (326)에서 샘플링하고있어 볼 수 있도록 잠금 공간에서이 작업을 수행 할 수
the exponent from the learning rate and then I'm raising it to the power of 10
하여 학습 속도와 지수와 나는 10의 힘으로 상승하고있어
amazing 10 to the power of it and so you don't want to just be sampling from a
그것의 전원을 10 놀라운 그래서 당신은 단지에서 샘플링되고 싶지 않아
uniform 0012 like a hundred because the most of your samples are kind of in a
귀하의 샘플의 대부분 때문에 백 같은 균일 한 0012은에 가지 있습니다
bad region right because the learning rate is a multiplicative interaction
불량 영역 바로 학습 속도가 곱셈 상호 작용 때문에
something to be aware of what works relatively well I'm doing a second pass
뭔가 비교적 잘 내가 두 번째 패스를하고있어 어떤 작품을 알고 있어야합니다
where I'm kind of going in and I'm changing these again a bit and i'm
어디 가지에 갈거야 그리고 난 다시 약간의 이러한 변화 그리고 난 해요
looking at what works so I find that I can now get 253 some of these work
그래서 어떤 작품을보고 난 지금이​​ 작업의 일부를 (253)를 얻을 수있는 것을 발견
really well one thing to be aware of sometimes you get a result like this
정말 잘 한 일이 가끔이 같은 결과를 얻을 알고 있어야합니다
53 is working quite well and this is actually worse if I see this I'm
(53)는 아주 잘 작동하고 난 난 이것을 볼 경우이 사실은 더 나쁘다
actually worried at this point because I'm so through this cross validation
나는이 교차 검증을 통해 너무이​​기 때문에 실제로이 시점에서 걱정
here I have a result here and there something actually wrong about this
여기에 나는 이것에 대해 실제로 뭔가 문제가 여기에 결과를 가지고
result that hints at some issue
일부 문제에서 힌트 결과
problem
문제
actually quite consistent too much happening here look amazing learning
사실은 꽤 일관성이 너​​무 여기에 일어나는 놀라운 학습 봐
rate between 93 94 tend to that and I end up with a very good result that is
93 (94) 사이의 속도는 경향 및 I는 아주 좋은 결과와 끝까지
just the boundaries of what I'm
난 무엇을 단지 경계
optimizing over so this is almost 13 it's almost 0001 which ends which is
이상 최적화하기 때문에 이것이 거의 13 그것은 거의 0001 인 끝나는이다
really a boundary of what I'm searching over some getting a really good result
정말 정말 좋은 결과를 얻는 몇 가지를 통해 찾고 있어요 무엇의 경계
at an edge of what I'm looking for and that's not good because maybe this year
의 가장자리에 내가 바라는 건 그게 잘되지 무슨 아마 올해 때문에
the way I've defined it is not actually optimal and so I want to make sure that
나는 그것을 정의한 방법은 실제로 최적이며, 그래서 있는지 확인하려면
I spot these things and I just my ranges because there might be even better
더 나은이있을 수 있기 때문에 나는이 일을 파악하고 난 그냥 내 범위
results
결과
going slightly this way so maybe I want to change negative 32 negative two or
내가 부정적인 변경하려면 어쩌면 약간이 길을가는 32 음의 두 개
2.5 and but for regularization I see that is working quite well so maybe i'm
2.5하지만 정규화에 대한 그게 어쩌면 내가 해요 아주 잘 작동 참조
in a slightly better spot and so I'm so worried about this one thing I like to
약간 더 나은 장소 등의 난을 좋아하는이 한 일에 대해 너무 걱정
point out as you'll see me sample bees randomly also tend to the uniform of
당신이 나를 샘플 꿀벌 무작위도의 균일 한 경향 볼로 지적
this some sampling random regularization learning return doing this what you
이 일이 어떤 샘플링 임의의 정규화 학습 복귀 무엇을
might see sometimes people do with what's called a grid search so really
사람들은 그래서 정말 그리드 검색이라고 무엇을 함께 할 때로 볼 수 있습니다
the difference here is instead of sampling randomly people like to go in
사람들이에 가고 싶어 무작위로 여기의 차이는 대신 샘플링입니다
steps of fixed amounts in both the learning rate and the regulation and so
학습 속도 조절 등 모두 일정량 씩
you end up with this double loop here over some settings of learning even some
당신은 심지어 학습의 일부 설정을 통해 여기 더블 루프 끝
settings of regularization
정규화의 설정
trying to be exhaustive and this is actually a bad idea doesn't actually
철저한 되려고 노력이이 실제로 나쁜 생각은 실제로하지 않습니다
work as well as a few simple randomly and unintuitive but you actually always
실제로 언제나 당신을 몇 무작위로 간단하고 직관적으로 잘 작동하지만,
want to sample randomly don't want to go into next steps and here's the reason
다음 단계로 가고 싶지 않아 무작위로 샘플링 할 여기에 이​​유가
for that it's kind of think about it but this is great search way so I sampled at
에 대한 그것의 종류 그것에 대해 생각이야 그러나 이것은 내가 샘플링 좋은 검색 방법입니다
set intervals and I can't have company you know sweep out the tax base and a
간격을 설정하고 난 당신이 과세 표준을 쓸어 알고있는 회사와을 가질 수 없습니다
random sampling where I just randomly sampled from the to the issue is that an
난 그냥 무작위로 문제로에서 샘플링 무작위 표본 추출은이다
optimization and training they're all that works what often happens is that
최적화 및 훈련 그들이 작동하는 모든 무엇 자주 발생하는 것으로되어있어
she's one of the parameters can be much much more important than the other
그녀는 매개 변수 중 하나가 훨씬 더 중요한 다른 것보다이 될 수있어
parameter
매개 변수
so say that this is an important parameter its performance the
그래서 이것은 중요한 파라미터이다라고 그 성능
performance of your loss function is not really a function of the white dimension
당신의 손실 함수의 성능은 정말 흰색 차원의 함수가 아니다
but it's really a function of the exhibition you get much better result in
하지만 정말 당신이 더 나은 결과를 얻을 전시의 함수이다
a specific range along the x-axis and if this is true then which is often the
종종 인 X 축을 따라이 다음에 해당되는 경우, 특정 영역
case then in this case you're actually going to end up something lots of
경우는이 경우에 당신은 실제로 뭔가를 많이 끝날거야
different taxes and you end up with a better spot than here where you've
다른 세금과 당신은 당신이했습니다 여기보다 더 좋은 자리와 끝까지
sampled at exact spot and you're not getting any kind of information across
정확한 지점에서 샘플링하면에 걸쳐 모든 종류의 정보를 얻기하지 않는
the ex if that makes sense so always use random because in these cases which are
그 말이 경우 전 그렇게 때문에 항상 있습니다 이러한 경우 임의 사용
common the random will actually give you more bang for the buck so I promise you
실제로 내가 약속 당신에게 벅에 대한 더 많은 강타를 줄 것이다 일반적인 임의
want to play with the most common ones are probably the learning rate the
아마 학습 속도를 수있는 가장 일반적인 사람과 놀고 싶어
update to type maybe we're going to we're going to go into this in a bit
업데이트는 어쩌면 우리가 조금이에 갈 거 야에 거 야를 입력합니다
the regularization and the dropout amount we're going to go into so this is
정규화와 드롭 아웃 금액은 우리는 그래서이가로 갈거야
really it's so much fun so in practice the way but this looks like as we have a
정말 너무 재미는 방법은 실제로 그래서 그러나 이것은 우리가를 가지고있는 것 같습니다
for example of computer vision cluster we have so many machines so I can just
컴퓨터 비전 클러스터의 예를 들어 우리는 그래서 난 그냥 수 많은 기계가
distributes my training across so many machines and I've written myself for
많은 기계에서 내 훈련을 배포하고 나는 자신을 작성했습니다
example comment and turned to face where these are all the loss functions on all
예를 들어 의견은 이러한 모든 모든 손실 기능이 어디 얼굴을 설정
the different machines and computers and cluster these are all here are some
다른 기계와 컴퓨터와이 여기에 모두 몇 가지 클러스터
searching over and I can see basically what's working and what isn't and I can
기본적으로 어떻게 작동하고 무엇을 통해 검색하고 내가 볼 수있는 것은 아니고, 내가 할 수있는
send commands to my workers so I can say ok this isn't working at all stages
내가 확인이 모든 단계에서 작동하지 않는 말을 할 수 있도록 내 노동자들에게 명령을 보낼
resample you're not doing well at all and some of these are doing very well
재 샘플 당신은 전혀 잘하지 않는 이들 중 일부는 아주 잘하고있다
and I look at what's exactly working well and I'm adjusting its a dynamic
나는 정확히 잘 작동하고 무엇을보고 나는 그에게 동적 조정 해요
process that I have to go through to actually get the stuff to work well
내가 통과해야 할 과정은 실제로 잘 작동하는 물건을 얻기 위해
because he just have too much stuff to optimize over and you can afford to just
그는 단지 너무 많은 물건을 가지고 있기 때문에 이상 최적화하고 당신은 단지에 여유가 있습니다
spray and pray you have to work with it
스프레이 당신이 함께 일해야기도
ok so you optimizing you're looking at a loss functions
확인 그래서 당신은 최적화 당신은 손실 함수에서 찾고
loss functions can take various different forms and you need to be able
손실 함수는 여러 가지 다른 형태를 취할 수 있으며, 당신은 할 수 있어야합니다
to read into what that means so you'll be you'll get quite good at looking at a
당신이보고에서 당신은 꽤 좋은거야있을거야, 그래서 그게 무슨 뜻인지에 읽기
loss function as an interesting what happens this one for example it was
그것이 예를 들어이 일을 무슨 재미로 손실 함수
pointing out that previous lecture it's not as exponential as a maybe used to my
아마에 사용 된 이전 강의가 같은 지수 아니라고 지적 내
loss functions I'd like it to you know it looks a little to linger and so that
당신이 그래서 우물쭈물하고 조금 보이는 알고에 손실 함수를 내가 원하는
maybe tells me that the learning rate as may be slightly too low so that doesn't
어쩌면이되지 않도록으로 학습 속도가 약간 너무 낮은 수 있음을 알려줍니다
mean the learning rate is too low just means that I might want to consider
학습 속도가 그냥 고려할 수 있음을 의미 너무 낮 의미
trying
견딜 수 없는
morning sometimes you get all kinds of funny things so you can have a plateau
당신이 고원을 가질 수 있도록 아침 때로는 재미 모든 종류의 것들을 얻을
where at some point that would decide that now runs you optimize usually so
어떤 시점에서 그 결정 것 인 지금 당신이 그렇게 일반적으로 최적화 실행
what is the prime suspect in these kinds of cases just a guess me and i think is
의 경우 이러한 종류의 유력한 용의자가 무엇 단지 저를 생각하고 나는 생각
the prime suspect you initialize correctly the gradients and barely
총리가 올바르게 그라디언트를 초기화하고 거의 의심
flowing but at some point they add up and just saw some research training so
흐르는하지만 어떤 점에서 그들은까지 추가하고 그냥 몇 가지 연구 훈련을 보았다
lots of fun in fact it's so much fun that I started an entire tumblr a while
사실 많은 재미가 내가 잠시 동안 전체 텀블러를 너무 재미있어 시작이
ago and lost function so they can go through these people contribute these
이 사람들이 이러한 기여를 통해 그들이 갈 수 있도록 전 및 기능을 상실
which is nice and services I think so and training especially transfer network
어떤 좋은 서비스 나는 그렇게 생각하고 훈련 특히 네트워크 전송
we're going to go into that this is all kinds of exotic shapes I'm not exactly
우리가이 들어갈거야 것은 이국적인 모양의 모든 종류 I 정확히 아니에요입니다
know at some point you're not really sure what any of this means it's going
이 중 하나는 그것이 무슨 의미인지 정말 모르는 어떤 점에서 알 수
so well
잘
yeah so here this several tasks that are training at the same time and just this
그래, 그래서 여기 몇 가지 동시에 훈련하는 작업과 그냥이
by the way I know what happened here it's this is actually training a
그런데 나는이 사실을 훈련한다 무엇을 여기에 무슨 일이 있었 알고
reinforcement learning agent the problem in reinforcement learning as you don't
그렇지으로 강화 학습 강화에 에이전트에게 문제를 학습
have a stationary distribution you don't have a fixed asset investment learning
만약 고정 자산 투자 학습 갖고 있지 않은 고정식 분포를 갖도록
agent interacting with the environment if your policy changes and you end up
정책 변화와 당신이 끝날 경우 에이전트 환경과 상호 작용
like staring at the wall or you end up looking at different parts of your space
벽에 응시하거나 당신의 공간의 다른 부분을보고 결국 같은
you end up with different data distributions and so suddenly I'm
당신은 다른 데이터 분포와 끝까지 그래서 갑자기 난
looking at something very different than what I used to be looking at and I'm
내가 사용하는 것보다 매우 다른 것을보고는보고있다 및 난
training my agent and lost goes up because the agent is unfamiliar with
내 에이전트를 훈련 손실은 에이전트가 익숙하기 때문에까지 간다
that kind of templates and so you have all kinds of fun stuff happening there
그 템플릿의 종류 그래서 당신은 재미있는 물건이 일어나고있는 모든 종류가있다
and then this one is one of my favorites I have no idea what basically happened
다음이 하나 내가 아무 생각이 무엇을 기본적으로 일어나지 않았을 내 즐겨 찾기 중 하나입니다
here this loss oscillates but roughly does and then it comes just explodes
여기 손실은 진동하지만 대략 수행하고 그냥 폭발 온다
clearly something was not right in this case and also here just got someone
분명히 뭔가가이 경우 오른쪽 않았고, 또한 여기에 그냥 사람이 있어요
decides to converge and no idea was wrong so you get all kinds of funny
수렴하기로하고 재미의 모든 종류를 얻을 수 있도록 아무 생각이 잘못 없었다
things if you end up with funny plots in your assignment please do send them to
일이 당신의 임무에 재미 플롯으로 끝날 경우에 보내 마십시오
Los Panchos but
트리오 로스 판초 스하지만,
robust during training
훈련 도중 강력한
don't only look at the loss function and other thing to look at is your accuracy
만 손실 함수와 보는 다른 것은 보지 않는 당신의 정확성이다
especially accuracies for example so you sometimes prefer looking at the accuracy
가끔 정확성을보고 선호하므로 특히 예를 들어 정확도
over what functions because accuracies are interpretable I know what these
무슨 기능을 통해 정확도는 해석하기 때문에 나는 어떤이 알고
classification accuracies mean in absolute terms for loss function is
손실 함수는에 대한 분류의 정확도는 절대적인 의미
maybe not as interpretable and so in particular I have a loss for my
아마로 해석 등 특히 난에 대한 손실이없는 내
salvation data and my training and so for example in this case I'm saying that
구원 데이터와 나의 훈련 때문에이 경우 예를 들어 나는 그 말을 해요
my training data accuracy is getting much much better and validation accuracy
내 트레이닝 데이터의 정확도가 훨씬 더 검증 정확성을 받고
has stopped improving and so based on this guy that can give you hints on what
당신에게 힌트를 줄 수있는이 사람에 따라 이렇게 개선 중지 것을
might be going on under the hood in this particular case there's a huge gap here
특히이 경우에 후드에 갈 수있는 큰 격차가 여기에있다
so maybe I'm thinking of overfitting
그래서 어쩌면 내가 overfitting 생각 해요
100% sure but I might be overpaying I might want to try to regular I strongly
100 % 확신하지만 난 강하게 나는 정기적으로 시도 할 수도 있습니다 과불 수 있습니다
when things might also be looking at is tracking the difference between the
물건도보고 될 수 있습니다 때의 차이를 추적
scale of your parameters and the scale of your updates to those parameters so
당신의 매개 변수의 규모와 그 매개 변수로 업데이트의 규모 때문에
say you're so you're suppose that your weights are on the order of unit gushing
당신이 당신의 무게 단위 분출의 순서에 있다고 가정하고 그래서있어 말
then intuitively the update that your incrementing your weights by and
다음 직관적으로 당신에 의해 당신의 무게를 증가 업데이트 및
back-propagation you don't want those updates to be much larger than the
역 전파 당신은보다 훨씬 큰 것으로 해당 업데이트를하지 않으
weights obviously or you want them to be tiny
분명히 가중치 또는 당신은 그들이 작은되고 싶어
your updates to be on the order of 1987 when your weights are on the order of
당신의 무게의 순서에있을 때 당신의 업데이트는 1987 년 정도가 될 수 있습니다
one negative too and so look at the update that you're about to increment
음 너무 그래서 당신이 증가하는 약이야 업데이트를 보면 하나
onto your weights and just look at this norm for example the color squares and
당신의 무게에 그냥 예를 들어,이 표준 보는 색상 사각형과
compared to the update the scale of your parameters and usually a good rule of
일반적으로 귀하의 매개 변수의 규모와의 좋은 규칙 업데이트에 비해
thumb is this should be roughly 13 so basically everything will update your
엄지 손가락이 대략 13 그래서 기본적으로 모든 업데이트 할 수 있어야 당신의
modifying on the order of like a third significant digits for every single
의 하나 하나에 대한 세 번째 유효 숫자와 같은 순서에 수정
parameter right you're not making huge updates you're not making very small
매개 변수를 오른쪽 당신은 당신이 매우 작은 결정하지 않는 거대한 업데이트를 제작하지 않는
updates so that's one thing to look at roughly 13 usually works ok if this is
그래서 업데이트는이 경우 일반적으로 확인 작동 대략 13를보고 한 가지
too high I want to maybe decrease my learning made its way too low like say
너무 높은 어쩌면 말 내 학습 등의 방법이 너무 낮게 감소 할
it's 107 maybe I want to increase my learning rate and so in summary today we
107 아마 내 학습 속도를 증가 할 그래서 요약 오늘날 우리 것
looked at a whole bunch of things to do with training neural networks the teal
교육 신경 네트워크 청록색 함께 할 수있는 일의 전체 무리 보았다
the arms of all of them are basically you lose track mean use the
그들 모두의 팔은 당신이 사용하는 트랙을 의미 잃게 기본적으로 있습니다
initialization
초기화
or if you think you have a small network you can maybe get away with just
당신은 당신이 작은 네트워크를 생각하는 경우 또는 당신은 어쩌면 그냥 멀리 얻을 수 있습니다
choosing your scale 2001 or maybe you want to play with that a bit and there's
당신의 규모 2001 선택하거나 어쩌면 당신은 그와 조금 놀고 싶어하고있다
no strong recommendation here I think just use and when you're doing I'm not
여기에 강한 권고 난 그냥 생각하지 사용할 때 당신은 내가 아니에요하고있는
my decision make sure to sample programs and doing lots base when appropriate and
내 결정 프로그램을 샘플링해야하고 많은에게 기부를 할 때 적절하고
that's something to be aware of and this is what we still have to cover and that
그주의해야 할 뭔가 이것은 우리가 아직도 충당하기 위해 무엇을하고 그
will be next we do have two more minutes so I will take questions if there are
이 경우 내가 질문을 할 수 있도록 우리가 두 분 이상을해야합니까 옆에있을 것입니다
any
어떤
correlation between
사이의 상관 관계
I don't think there's any obviously I can recommend there you have to get a
나는 어떤 분명히 당신이 얻을 필요가 추천 할 수 있다고 생각하지 않습니다
check of it I don't think there's anything jumps out at me that's obvious
그 검사는 그게 분명 나를 밖으로 점프 거기에 아무것도 생각하지 않습니다
another couple in ok great questions
확인 위대한 질문에서 다른 커플
question regarding
에 대한 질문